Gosh, I'm tired.
(Jin Ho looks through his notebook
in the morning.)
I had a lot on my mind.
Up until that point,
I had taken a step back.
I focused on assisting my team
while Xitsuh and Seong Beom took charge.
That was the position I had played.
But Xitsuh got eliminated.
Letting Seong Beom lead the team alone
might be too much for him.
I decided to play alongside Seong Beom...
and contribute more to lead the team.
I don't know.
- I'm sure it'll require us to team up.
- Right.
- There are 10 of us yet.
- Yes, there are 10 of us.
Excluding Beom, Seung Yong, and Ji Hoo,
there are seven of us.
Depending on whose side Sung Joo joins,
it will be either 6 to 4 or 7 to 3.
He'll probably team up with them.
So it might be 6 to 4.
For our alliance to make sense...
and to lead our alliance,
we need people.
We're playing individually now.
If we get a game
where teaming up makes sense,
I will...
try my best not to repeat...
yesterday's tragic outcome.
I want to be a reliable shield
for my teammates.
Gosh, it will be...
too much for me
if I end up going to the Deathmatch.
Let's get a clean win.
Winning the Money Challenge
looks like our best option.
You're right. Let's win, plain and simple.
I'm getting used to Bloody Game X.
When I heard the rules
in the beginning of the shoot,
I used to think, "Gosh, what kind of game
are we supposed to play?"
It looked like I wasn't quite fitting in.
Now, it's different.
We get the rules from the screen.
I'm starting to see
how I'm supposed to play the games now.
What should we do
for the anti-jinx ritual this morning?
It's a thing we do every morning.
"All right,
I'll probably be going home today."
Then I do something.
Yesterday, I wrote down my phone number
and gave it to him.
- I see.
- With this ritual, we keep surviving.
When I told him, "We had a good run,"
we survived again.
When I said, "Call me when you get out,"
we survived once again.
So I must do something again.
I already packed my suitcase.
But Tae Gyun hadn't packed at all.
I guess preparing for departure
prevents us from going home.
There must be energy working against it.
I should pack my suitcase too
on my way down.
I should close it up neatly too.
- You're already back.
- Yes.
I just ate.
I've been thinking in the shower.
I want to go home,
but it'd be a pity to go home
after I made it this far.
- I agree.
- I do want to go home,
but I'd hate to see Seung Yong advance.
Exactly.
I want to go home,
but I'd hate to lose to Seung Yong.
Part of me also thought it wasn't fair...
how Xitsuh got eliminated so early
in the competition.
As his former teammate,
I felt it wasn't fair
that I couldn't protect him in any way.
Please gather in the main hall.
Good morning.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
You're wearing a short-sleeve shirt,
not a tank top.
- I'm wearing my regular clothes.
- Hey.
He should've gone to the outdoor
survival grounds in that outfit.
- Me too. Thank you.
- Well, we haven't...
- Did you get some sleep?
- Pardon?
Did you get some sleep after betraying us?
I drank so much.
He betrayed you?
No. I moved to a bigger room.
Back to Team P2's room.
It must be nice
having the room all to yourself.
- It's nice.
- Right.
What am I still doing here?
I've been placing last since Day One.
I got eliminated once.
I was sent to the basement.
- My gosh.
- Exactly.
Every time I wake up and come down
to play, I keep finding you sitting here.
Right. I just sit here. That's all.
This guy doesn't seem to go away
how hard we try to get rid of him.
Somehow, I'm still here.
I guess I have a lot of good luck
this year.
I kicked him out,
but he found his way back.
- He keeps coming back.
- Right.
I can't even count
how many times you came back.
Exactly.
Before explaining the rules,
the winning benefits
of the Money Challenge will be announced.
The winner will receive 20,000 dollars...
and two elimination immunity passes.
One of the elimination immunity passes
can be transferred to another player.
Today's Deathmatch
will require three players.
The bottom two players will be up...
for elimination by default.
The two bottom players will single out...
a player each,
and a vote will be held
for the chosen players.
(They will pick a player each.
There will be a vote for the 2 players.)
The player with the most votes
and the two bottom players...
In other words, a total of three players
will participate in...
a three-way Deathmatch.
Excluding the winner of the Deathmatch,
the other two players will be eliminated.
They will have to leave Bloody Game X.
- There's only one survivor.
- Today's Money Challenge...
will be revealed now.
- Please.
- Today's Money Challenge is...
(Project Galaxy)
Project Galaxy.
Do you know this game?
Not at all.
Project Galaxy is an individual match,
featuring ten players.
Players must guess the location...
of the hidden celestial objects
through observations.
Their goal is
to score the highest points...
while utilizing the variable,
the black hole.
The game board consists
of 16 circular sectors,
numbered 1 through 16.
A comet, a planet, a satellite,
twin clouds, a dwarf planet, a star,
and cosmic dust.
A total of seven celestial objects
are hidden...
across the sectors,
each governed by its own rules.
The locations of the celestial objects
will be confidential.
The game consists of ten rounds.
Each round will last 30 minutes.
Players must guess the locations
of the celestial objects.
To find celestial objects
that yield higher points,
they must choose a sector
to stay in for the round.
Before Round One begins,
a basic hint will be revealed
to help the players guess the locations.
Before each odd-numbered round begins,
an additional hint will be revealed
for one minute.
All players will receive 30 coins...
as starting capital.
Players will enter the Voting Room
every round...
and can choose
to do 1 of the 4 following actions.
The first action is observing.
Players can designate...
up to eight consecutive sectors
once per round...
and ask how many celestial objects
are located within the selected range.
When doing so, players are allowed...
to narrow down the search range
by spending coins.
One coin is required for each sector
narrowed down.
From Rounds 1 through 8,
the observation ranges
are already specified.
Starting from Round Nine,
players can freely choose...
any eight consecutive sectors
without being restricted to any set range.
However, stars will be excluded
from the observation targets.
When observed,
they will be seen as cosmic dust.
The second action is moving a sector.
Players are required
to pick a sector to stay in...
each round.
In Round One,
they can freely pick any sector they want.
But starting from Round Two,
they can only move their sector,
adjacent to the one
they occupied in the previous round.
To move beyond adjacent sectors,
players must pay one coin
per sector skipped.
If a player fails to pick a sector
within the time limit,
the player will lose five points
for the round.
By the end of the round,
only players who are lined up...
in front of the Voting Room
will be allowed.
The third action is
betting on a black hole.
A black hole exists in a sector
every round.
A black hole reverses the point values...
of the current sector
and the two adjacent ones.
A black hole will start off
in the first sector.
The black hole advances one sector
clockwise every round.
Players can shift the black hole
additional sectors by betting their coins.
At the end of the round, the black hole...
moves additional sectors,
selected by the player...
with the highest bet.
If two or more players tie
for the highest bet,
the choice...
of the next highest bidder will apply.
The fourth action is checking the score.
Players can check...
their cumulative score by spending coins.
In Round 1, players must spend 10 coins.
With each passing round,
the cost decreases by one coin.
At the end of the round,
points earned in the round...
will be revealed, which will also
reflect the effect of the black hole.
The earned points will be revealed...
anonymously under designated letters
from A to J.
The assigned letters will remain unchanged
until the game ends.
At the end of 10 rounds,
the 2 players with the lowest scores...
will participate in the Deathmatch.
(They will participate in the Deathmatch.)
The player with the highest score...
will receive
two elimination immunity passes.
One of the passes can be transferred
to another player.
Two players heading to the Deathmatch...
will choose one player each...
from those
without an elimination immunity pass.
Then they'll vote to pick the last player
for the Deathmatch.
If players tie,
the player with more coins...
or the player with more personal funds
will win.
Three items are available
in Project Galaxy.
The first item is
the Player Location Check Card.
Players can pick one player...
and find out the sector
the player stayed in the previous round.
The second item is extra coins.
Players can buy five extra coins.
The third item is a hidden item.
It will be revealed
before the start of Round Six.
In the second season, I cursed Pi out...
while playing the Money Challenge.
This is a similar Money Challenge.
I need to be in the sector
with the highest points...
and earn as many points as possible
in that round.
The key point is widening...
the point difference every round.
Forming an alliance is
the ultimate winning strategy.
I thought that forming a solid alliance...
would give me an upper hand.
If I were to win, I could use
one immunity pass for myself...
- and transfer one to someone else.
- You could transfer the other one.
My gosh. In the end,
playing as an alliance will be tricky.
Let's say we form a three-player alliance.
There are only
two elimination immunity passes.
- One of them won't be protected. Right?
- Yes.
We can save the third player
through the vote.
The benefit for the winning player...
was two elimination immunity passes.
I thought that one of the passes
could be transferred.
During this season, we rarely got
these elimination immunity passes.
I was surprised to hear this benefit.
This is the perfect card
to drive people to betray one another.
In the end,
this game requires an alliance.
- Yes.
- Right.
- It's a game of information.
- It's all about information.
We can ask one question each.
With 4 people, that's 4 questions.
With 6 people, that's 6 questions.
There are so many things
you can figure out with just one question.
An extra player could make
two differences.
Go and get YunB.
We spread out to earn points.
We picked a specific sector...
to earn 2 or 4 points.
Do you remember that?
Ji Hoo, Seung Yong, Sung Joo, and me.
It was the four of us.
We just needed to recruit one more player.
We had Sung Joo on our side.
YunB came back.
I thought we could form a team with YunB.
It could be a 5-on-5 match.
(Beom is on the move to recruit YunB.)
(Securing a spot next to him)
- Oh, that?
- Yes, the legend.
My goodness. Hold on.
Will they bring in the board?
No. You have to get on a spaceship
and leave Earth.
- For real?
- There's a telescope.
My gosh.
I have to visualize this in my head.
Can I rely on you, Ji Min?
You weren't there for this game
in the second season.
It's easier than you think.
- Wait, I'll play with you then.
- Okay.
You know,
- we need to team up with the majority.
- Seriously.
You know that, right?
Once we pool our information,
we know everyone's locations and bets.
We just have to avoid the worst.
You've got to be James Bond.
- Me?
- What's your name?
James Bond.
- We have to team up for this, right?
- Definitely.
- The more people, the better?
- Yes.
That's because...
You...
need to pretend
that you're teaming up with us.
As for what you're asking,
I can do it. But I don't have the talent
to pull it off.
There are aspects of a card game too.
This is crazy.
I thought, "What's going on?"
"What's Sung Joo doing there?"
"Wait."
If we play with Seung Yong today,
we'll be doomed.
Why?
Destroying him is their plan.
You should run.
The overall consensus was that
they wanted to eliminate Seung Yong.
So many people mentioned that to me.
Actually, I wasn't the only one.
Everyone showed strong hostility
toward them.
As it so happened,
many of us were in the same boat.
Seong Beom and Hye Seon...
had to say goodbye to Xitsuh
who was like a mom to them.
For someone who had to watch
Xitsuh and Tae Gyun leave the show,
there was a clear target to blame.
So I tried to drive the narrative
against them.
I said, "Having more people
on our team would be better."
"We should play together."
I was determined to recruit Sung Joo.
I think YunB might be good at this.
I think he played a similar game
in the second season.
He did. And he played well.
He won first place.
(Clueless of the current situation,
they're hoping to play a 5-on-5 match.)
- Seung Yong.
- Yes?
Are you busy with the rules?
- What is it?
- Are you busy now?
I think you're their target.
Okay.
Let's think about that
while going over the rules.
They discussed it.
- Targeting me?
- Yes.
There's nothing I can do.
If we recruit YunB,
a 5-on-5 match won't be a bad deal for us.
If it's a 5-on-5 match...
As long as we're not outnumbered,
- It's good.
- we won't lose.
- It will be tough...
- But a 6-on-4 match...
if it becomes a 6-on-4 match.
- Do you have a lighter?
- It's so uncomfortable.
- I have a lighter.
- Are you anxious?
I'm stuck in the middle.
I don't know which side to join.
You have to join my side.
- Your side? As in Ji Min's side?
- There's a reason for it.
Yes. Ji Min and Jin Ho.
The perfect place to become wallpaper.
- But it's nice.
- I think we'd win, though.
But the other team is pretty good too.
One of them is like a supercomputer.
What will you do?
- I'm doomed.
- What?
- I need to give up on our alliance.
- Why?
I need to join the other team.
So you want to join them too?
I'm in a position
where I have that option.
I have that option.
But...
we can have a 5-on-5 match
if you join us, YunB.
- That's true.
- Yes.
Isn't it better to even the playing field
by making it a 5-on-5 match?
But from what I heard...
after coming back to the show,
things got out of hand on the Heist Day.
Seung Yong now has a giant target
on his back.
There's nothing we can do about it.
- It's pretty bad.
- After the Heist Day?
It's that bad?
- We didn't know. But we found out later.
- Yes.
And yesterday's game didn't help either.
They're pretty upset...
because they tried
to send Jin Ho and Xitsuh home.
That only added fuel to the fire.
Right. I can see that.
- Yes. But...
- But as for me,
- You'll play with him?
- I'll play with him.
If I switch teams too,
it will crush Seung Yong.
- Right. I understand your position.
- So... Yes.
- Switching teams now...
- Okay.
just to save my own neck...
- isn't right.
- Okay.
You also think it's important
to have more people on your team, right?
- Of course.
- This game is about information.
- It's all about information.
But...
now that I talked to you guys,
- You should join us.
- it looks like it will be 7 against 3.
I'll still play with the minority.
Tell them I tried to recruit YunB,
but I failed,
so I'm joining them instead.
- What?
- Tell them I failed to recruit YunB,
- so I'm joining them instead.
- You don't want a target on your back?
For me to ditch Teams R and C
and join the other team,
I need some kind of insurance...
because of the elimination system.
- You'll play with us?
- Yes.
I still have a problem if I join you.
They can pick two players.
- They'll pick me for sure.
- What?
They'll see me as a traitor.
I did betray them.
Our team only gets two immunity passes.
- Right. We'll give you the pass.
- Can I get the pass?
In return, I won't play a double agent.
- Right. I know that you're not that type.
- Then...
- those two have to agree too.
- Okay.
- Yes. Or I...
- Yes.
He's saying that...
if he betrays them and joins us,
they will pick him for sure.
I hate to say this,
but those three are cowards.
So they'll pick the weakest players.
You have a point,
but Sung Joo feels nervous about it.
So he said if he gets the immunity pass,
he'll do his best to win the game.
If you promise me the pass,
I won't sabotage the team.
Were you coming to join us to sabotage us?
- Of course, not.
- If you didn't get the pass?
It's obvious what's going to happen to me.
I have a 50 percent chance
of getting chosen if we win.
of getting chosen if I join them and lose.
I don't think they would pick you...
even if you were to join us
and we were to win.
I do agree with them.
It's iffy.
If we were to decide that now,
it would distract me
from focusing on the game.
- There are other variables.
- We should talk when everyone's here.
Here's what's most important.
One of us will be the winner.
When I asked them
to give me the immunity pass,
it seemed like too big of a benefit
although I was joining them...
to help them.
So we had to meet in the middle
to make a deal.
That's why I came up with this deal.
All right.
So when it comes to making the decision...
I know that I'm switching teams now.
I hope you'd treat me the same way...
as the rest of them.
- Absolutely.
- Of course.
- Don't try to get me eliminated.
- You don't have to worry about that.
We're not like that. I don't know
what kind of team you've been playing...
We had a level-headed discussion.
I made a compromise and wasn't so greedy.
That's how it started.
I also think the immunity pass is
a bit too much for me.
- So I want to be treated equally.
- Of course.
First of all, we're outnumbered.
- You must know that.
- It's 6 against 4?
It's not even 6 against 4.
- Then?
- It will be 7 against 3.
- Because of Sung Joo?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Why?
If you think about it,
Sung Joo is a member of Team P2.
- Okay.
- He did join our team...
later in the competition.
It's iffy to leave YunB
all alone with them.
We can't recruit YunB?
I don't think so. Their alliance...
- is too solid.
- What did you hear?
- Let me be completely honest.
- Okay.
Seung Yong is their target.
Their discussion dates back
to the Heist Day.
- Come on.
- You're everyone's target now.
- Really?
- This whole game is built on that.
- Darn.
- This is their quest.
Their quest is...
to destroy Shin Seung Yong,
the Public Enemy.
Sung Joo was trying to recruit...
- even me, but I said it wasn't right.
- Okay.
I told them I would play with you
even if I ended up going home for it.
On the Heist Day,
I got carried away during the game.
My behavior that night...
gave them a reason to come after me.
So they talked about targeting me
and that's how it happened.
- So that's how it happened.
- Yes. They...
- Okay.
- already...
finished forming an alliance.
- I see. It's already done.
- Yes.
Sung Joo, so you've switched sides?
I told Beom everything.
My gosh, this one is going to be hard.
Let's think about that together.
I thought you were going to join us.
- I wanted to join you.
- Okay.
- I do want to play with you.
I want to play with Beom too.
To be honest with you,
I still have to consider justification.
So it's a bit iffy.
Do you have an issue
with Seung Yong as well?
No. Not at all.
If it's a 5-on-5 match,
it will be a lot more fun.
But...
I have to consider my position too.
I just made it back into the mansion.
I'm neutral.
They came to me first
and tried to win me over to their side.
I tried my best to change their mind.
With Sung Joo and YunB on our side,
it would be a 5-on-5 match
and we'd have a shot.
We'd be able to win no matter what
if I did the math right.
But...
- the thing is,
- Yes.
- they fooled me.
- What do you mean?
"Fool" isn't the right word.
I ended up joining their alliance.
(Inhaling sharply)
- Why, though?
- Well, you know...
Why don't you hear Seung Yong out?
We even pleaded to them.
We pleaded to them.
I also talked to Keun Woo.
But he wouldn't even budge.
Keun Woo.
So you're joining them, right?
- I'm with Ji Min.
- Right.
- How about playing separately for once?
- No way.
- I never switch sides.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Gosh, it was crazy.
I had never talked to Hye Seon before.
We barely talked during games.
I begged Hye Seon to join us.
They can just admit that they want
to destroy us by outnumbering us.
But they keep coming up
with a weird excuse.
I don't think it will be a fair fight.
Honestly, I don't get it. Yesterday,
everyone said it was just a game
and tomorrow was a different day.
They told us to do our best
although it got tough yesterday.
But all of a sudden today,
they got so petty
and changed their stance.
This doesn't look right.
If we're talking
about people's past mistakes,
should I mention their mistakes
outside the show too?
They're basically saying,
"We don't like him."
"So we want to eliminate him."
- That's how I see it.
- Okay.
I want to have a fair fight.
Would you?
Give me some time.
- I'll think about it.
- Yes, think about it.
They do have a reason to do this.
But this is a cowardly move.
- I know what you mean.
- Yes.
So...
So we might be able to turn it
into a fair game of 5 against 5.
- You should go and...
- We have a lot of time left.
They were talking a lot
with the other team.
I don't know what there could possibly be
to talk about.
I tried to focus on the game instead.
Taking the reasons into account,
I'm completely neutral.
Excluding the backstory
and everything else,
probability-wise, I think
the other team has a better chance...
at winning the game.
But if I were to fluff up...
and rationalize
what's happening right now,
they're forcing this whole justification.
Who do you think will get chosen
by the bottom two players?
I'm pretty sure it'd be me
even if I were to join your team.
No. If my team ends up losing,
I'll have the lowest score.
Come on.
No. I...
That's my point.
- I need a bargaining chip too.
- I see.
(Hesitant)
- I'm offering you a deal.
- Right.
- But...
- As for my reason behind joining them,
there's only one.
It has to do with Sung Joo.
If I were to explain my decision
in terms of backstories and history,
both of us came back from elimination.
So it only makes sense
that I join the team he joins.
That's why.
Parting ways with Sung Joo...
doesn't feel right to me.
When I talked to YunB,
he told me it was Sung Joo's decision.
When I talked to Sung Joo,
he said it was YunB's decision.
I started to get angry at that point.
So what do you want to do?
Do you want to play with them?
I can't switch sides again
like a turncoat.
- I should join them.
- No, you can join us.
- Well...
- We have a lot of time. Don't back down.
- It's uncomfortable.
- Come here, Sung Joo.
So you'll stick with them no matter what?
I can't switch sides again.
It was a tough decision.
Having more people would allow us to ask
more questions, and that'd be nice.
Darn it. We can only ask three questions.
Well, Beom is coming down.
(I see.)
- It's okay. Don't worry about that.
- Okay.
My gosh, it's uncomfortable.
What if I were to persuade Hye Seon
by telling her you'd join us?
It would be 5 against 5 then.
That might change things...
if you could persuade Hye Seon.
Beom. But here's your chance
of persuading her.
It's 0.01 percent.
I'll make...
- that 0.01 percent chance happen.
- Okay.
You should keep an open mind then, YunB.
- You said you were neutral.
- Leave a 50 percent chance open for us.
- I...
I'll keep an open mind.
Let me keep trying.
There was nothing I could do.
If I were to recruit you,
YunB might join us too.
(Beom tries to persuade Hye Seon.)
We can make it into a 5-on-5 match.
- Mr. YunB.
- Yes?
I'll go to the Deathmatch.
That has to be our strategy.
There's no other way.
They're going out to talk now.
I'm trying to recruit them.
I made a deal with them...
telling them that I'd go to the
Deathmatch. That's what I offered them.
To win, we should use my coins
in the beginning.
The best strategy is
making one of us win the whole thing.
That's the best strategy.
- Here's what crossed my mind.
- Yes.
I don't feel good about this either.
- We're ganging up on them?
- Yes. So...
It is what it is.
Think about the probability.
Survival is important to you too.
- It is what it is.
- This is annoying.
You have the biggest reason...
to stay with them.
- You do have a point.
- Yes.
- I was so sad to see Xitsuh go.
- Right.
And I'll be honest.
I didn't have to think about this
even for 0.0001 percent.
Telling him I'd think about his offer...
was also my strategy.
I didn't want any bad blood between us.
There's even one percent chance that
they might pick me for the Deathmatch.
So I kept turning him down politely...
not to get on his bad side.
- Twenty percent from the Heist Day.
- Yes.
Another 20 percent
because you were on Team P3...
and played
with Seong Beom and Jin Ho before.
- Yes, you're right.
- Right.
Considering everything,
I don't see any point to switch.
Don't you agree?
I'm looking for the lowest chance
of getting eliminated.
My goal is to survive.
Of course, I'd join the majority.
It's a no brainer.
I see. You're right.
So that's why I decided like this.
I see. Great. Thank you.
- You helped me clear things up.
- Okay.
It's important to justify our decisions.
What should we do?
Well, we've made our decision.
I don't think Hye Seon can be persuaded.
Well, I can't switch teams
for the same reasons I told you earlier.
- I can't force you. Games are just games.
- Right.
What was that? Oh, the Heist Day. Even if
we exclude the things of the Heist Day...
- That's it.
- There's nothing we can do.
- Let's have a good game then.
- Okay.
- Can I talk to you one last time?
- Sure.
You don't have any personal funds.
- What?
- You don't have any personal funds.
- Right. I have no money.
- I can...
- Yes.
- Money?
Well, that doesn't make
a lot of difference.
Money doesn't matter.
Well, you can buy items with the money.
I told everything to Beom.
I was transparent with him.
- I see.
- So he could understand my situation.
I'm trying to join the team
with the lowest chance of elimination.
I don't have any money.
Joining the majority is the simplest
for me.
I'm still neutral.
We can play together tomorrow
if there's a chance.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
I'll teach you how to rap too.
Good.
(The Majority Alliance has been finalized
with 7 players.)
I'll just sit here. It's okay.
(The Minority Alliance has been finalized
with 3 players.)
- There's nothing we can do.
- Right. This is how it will go.
- We can do it.
I don't know.
I just think it's a group of petty people.
They kept coming up with excuses.
By that logic,
people can start killing each other...
just for looking at them.
It's like they want to eliminate us for
not following them back on social media.
How far will they go back in time
to come up with an excuse?
"He glared at me on the day
when we untied the rope."
"I'll kill him."
How about that for an excuse?
It was super infuriating.
I couldn't let my anger show.
There's nothing we can do.
I'll make you advance no matter what.
- What?
- I'll make you advance.
What should we do?
The 1st hint will be revealed
for 1 minute.
(Revealing the first hint)
"At least one pair of twin clouds is..."
"adjacent to a satellite."
Let's go and check.
To a satellite?
It's adjacent to a satellite.
There are four pairs of twin clouds.
At least two or more pairs are adjacent
to one another.
Depending on the number
of twin clouds sectors players occupy,
all the players can earn up
to three points.
However, if all four twin clouds sectors
are occupied with players,
all the players will lose three points.
Planets and satellites are next.
There is only 1 planet.
And there are 2 satellites.
They are located
in the eight consecutive sectors.
The number of players
in the planet sector...
is compared to the total number
of players across both satellite sectors.
Everyone in the majority sector
receives three points each.
If the player counts are tied,
everyone in both sectors
will lose three points each.
(At least 1 pair of twin clouds is
adjacent to a satellite.)
Taking the first hint into consideration,
satellites are located
next to the twin clouds.
(Twin clouds, satellite)
Okay. That's a big piece of information.
It means satellites are situated
next to the twin clouds.
The three of them come as a set.
You know what I think?
Teaming up in the beginning
might be tough.
- Yes.
- That won't be easy.
- Splitting up might be better.
- Playing as a team might be hard.
We should do that.
That way, we'll see how people score
on their own.
That will give us more information.
You're right. We should split up.
Round One begins now.
In Round 1,
players can observe Sectors 1 through 8.
The black hole is in Sector One.
- We can see where it is on the screen.
- It tells us where it is.
Which sector do we want?
What?
We should avoid losing points for now.
Winning 1st place? Well, to win 1st place,
getting the star sector would be best.
If we know where it is,
we'll place the black hole in that sector.
We have to start betting
on the black hole.
What should we do?
Well...
It's tough
since we don't have a lot of coins.
Asking a question
seems like the right move.
Let's go in order...
and take one object each. One at a time...
Our strategy in the beginning was simple.
We had a lot of people on our team.
There were seven of us.
So we asked about all of them.
We started from the top.
A satellite, a comet, a star,
a dwarf planet, and so on.
The range was from Sectors 1 through 8.
So we each asked a question.
Hye Seon, you take the comet.
- Okay.
- You take...
- Go ahead. We can't waste time.
- And...
you take the planet.
Ask how many planets
there are in Sectors 1 through 8.
- You...
- Ji Min, you take the satellites.
- Okay.
- You take the twin clouds.
Ask if there are twin clouds
in Sectors 1 through 8.
Hello.
How may I help you?
In Sectors 1 through 8,
how many comets are there?
- There's only one.
- Okay. Thank you.
In Sectors 1 through 8,
(Twin clouds)
are there any twin clouds?
There are 2 twin clouds
in Sectors 1 through 8.
In Sectors 1 through 8,
how many dwarf planets are there?
There's only one.
Is there a planet in Sectors 1 through 8?
- One comet?
- One comet.
Two twin clouds.
- There are 2 twin clouds?
- In Sectors 1 through 8.
There's 1 planet in Sectors 1 through 8.
There's one planet?
- The planet is in this range?
- Yes.
Give me 1 piece of information
during Round 10.
- Please?
- Come on, Beom.
Just one.
If we're winning by a landslide?
We can gather most of our information...
from the twin clouds.
- The three sectors come as a set.
- Right.
- We can figure out three sectors at once.
- Twin clouds...
I thought about the object
that would give us the most information.
Twin clouds sectors are adjacent
to each other.
A satellite sector
is also adjacent to them.
We can locate 3 sectors
if we figure out just 1 of them.
So we focused on locating them.
There are two twin clouds sectors...
in Sectors 1 through 8.
Okay. I got it.
(Observation: Twin clouds, 2)
(The Minority Alliance uses
1 of their 3 questions.)
There are 2 twin clouds sectors
in Sectors 1 through 8.
But we can't locate all of them.
- There's a total of four twin clouds.
- Right.
What should we ask next?
Let me think for a bit.
Should we narrow down the range
to Sectors 3 through 6?
Ask if there are twin clouds
in that range?
Yes. Narrowing down the range
sounds right.
- I'll go.
- Wait.
I thought
it was most important to locate...
the celestial objects
by asking the right questions.
My biggest dilemma was figuring out...
how I was going to do that.
Are there any satellites
in Sectors 1 through 8?
There are 2 satellites
in Sectors 1 through 8.
There are two satellites.
- Both of the satellites are in the range?
- Two satellites.
Then all of them are
in Sectors 1 through 8.
- Planets and satellites are in the range.
- They're in Sectors 1 through 8.
Coincidentally,
each celestial object was in the range.
The satellite and comet were
all in the range.
Two pairs of twin clouds
were in the range too.
(The Majority Alliance is quickly
gathering information.)
I think we should locate the twin clouds.
- That could be faster.
- Yes.
Once we locate the twin clouds,
it means a satellite is adjacent to them.
To locate the twin clouds,
we should change the range.
How many sectors...
should we get rid of from 1 through 8?
Should we do 2 or 3?
- Should we get rid of 3?
- Let's get rid of 3.
- One through five?
- Five. Yes.
If there's only one, we hit the jackpot.
- That means it's right on the border.
- They must be in Sectors 5 and 6.
In Sectors One...
through...
Five,
are there any twin clouds?
You need three coins to ask that question.
Will you spend your coins?
Yes, I will.
(1 coin is required for each sector
narrowed down in the question.)
This is my capital for gambling.
Here.
In Sectors 1 through 5,
there are two twin clouds.
Two?
Okay.
What did she say?
She doesn't know either.
Two.
- Two in Sectors One through Five?
- Two.
We must narrow down the range again.
So they're not in Sectors 6, 7, and 8.
Right.
We have to spend a lot of coins
on this question. One, three...
No. Here's how we can phrase the question.
Narrow it down to Sectors 3 through 8.
- I see.
- We can figure out...
if they are in Sectors 3, 4, or 5
just with 3 coins.
I'll spend two coins.
Are there twin clouds
in Sectors 3 through 8?
There are two twin clouds...
in Sectors 3 through 8.
(Observation: Twin clouds, 2)
When I asked my question,
by comparing the overlapped range
between Jin Ho's question and mine,
I was able to deduce that there were
2 twin clouds in Sectors 3 through 5.
There are 2 in Sectors 3 through 5?
If that's the case, Sector Four...
- must be the twin clouds.
- For sure.
- That's certain.
- It must be Sector Four.
- Sector Four...
- Right.
We'll be able to score
if we all choose this sector.
(The Majority Alliance locates 1 pair
of twin clouds.)
It doesn't have to be super early
in the game.
Our goal is to gather all the information
by Round Four.
- Having that as our goal would be nice.
- Because...
We can ask four more questions than them.
We'll be okay
as long as we ask the right questions.
(Observation: Twin clouds, 2)
(The Minority Alliance must locate
the twin clouds...)
(with only 2 observations remaining.)
This is tough.
We have to narrow down the range
in the end.
- We need to ask questions.
- Is it a bad idea to ask...
if there's a satellite
in Sectors 3 through 6?
That makes things more difficult.
- It's better to ask about twin clouds.
- Yes.
Let's ask if the twin clouds are
in Sectors 3 through 6.
How many twin clouds are there
in Sectors 3 through 6?
You need four coins to ask that question.
- Will you spend your coins?
- I will.
I can buy firewood and fire steel
with these coins.
There are two pairs of twin clouds...
in Sectors 3 through 6.
Let's spend my personal funds
to buy the items.
I have the highest probability
of going to the Deathmatch.
Let's spend my funds first.
How much money do you have?
I have 40,000 dollars.
I have 30,000 dollars.
I don't even have that much money.
Darn it. This is bad.
I'm sorry about this.
- No.
- You got stuck with me.
I won't join them even if they invite me.
- Jin Ho.
- Did you finish asking questions?
Let's make it 6 against 4.
Who is that?
(Observation: Twin clouds, 2)
Okay.
Let's narrow it down
and go with Sectors 4 and 5.
- Sectors 4 and 5?
- Hold on.
Should we go with Sectors 1 through 4?
We can exclude them.
- We can exclude Sectors 1, 2, 7, and 8.
- To save coins?
We don't have to narrow it down
to Sectors 4 and 5.
It'd be awesome if there's only 1 pair
of twin clouds...
- in Sectors 1 through 5.
- Yes.
It'd be iffy if we end up with two pairs.
Even if we have to spend one more coin,
shouldn't we go...
- with Sectors 1 through 4?
- Then...
We can pick Sectors 2, 1, and 0.
- Right.
- You're right.
We can locate them for sure then.
Yes, let's narrow it down
to Sectors 1 through 4.
That's right. We'll know
if the range has 1 or 2 twin clouds then.
(The Minority Alliance asks
the final observation question.)
Hi.
How many twin clouds are there...
from Sectors 1 to 4?
(Shin Seung Yong used 4 coins.)
From Sectors 1 to 4,
there's one twin cloud.
(1 twin cloud from Sectors 1 to 4)
Gosh, you scared me.
- The Orion...
- We should ask about the Orion.
One.
There's 1 from Sectors 1 to 4,
- so it's 4 and 5!
- Yes.
(The Minority Alliance has figured out
the twin clouds' position.)
(Twin clouds)
We got it with just three questions.
I know, right?
We took half of the total range,
then split that in half again to see...
whether it fell within
that half-range or not.
In just three observations,
we located two twin clouds.
It was exciting.
"Wait, this might work out."
"We might win."
With just one more member,
we could get the satellite position.
Seriously, what a huge bummer.
We'd find everything with one more member.
(Confirmed celestial object positions)
(Majority Alliance, Minority Alliance)
We have to go with our gut.
- It's either in 3, 4, or 5.
- Yes.
In the first round,
we can go anywhere we want.
But after that, we can only move
one sector per turn.
We can't move as a team.
Say that we split up.
Someone gets five points.
- They are in a star sector, no doubt.
- True.
That'd be a lucky break.
Our top priority was the star.
The only way seven members
could earn many points in one go...
was by finding the star.
So our goal was to find the star...
as quickly as possible.
Only one star exists.
It is not adjacent to any dwarf planet...
and appears as cosmic dust when observed.
Landing in the star sector
earns you five points.
Whenever a player scores points
from a star,
the star's energy increases by one...
at the end of that round.
(Star's energy)
When the star's energy reaches four,
it explodes and becomes a supernova.
Starting from the following round,
any player who lands
in the supernova sector loses five points.
- There's a comet here, right?
- Yes.
Land in the comet alone,
- and they'd get five points.
- Right.
There are three comets in total,
and they only appear
in even-numbered sectors.
(Comets: 3, only in even-numbered sectors)
To score points in a comet sector,
you must be the only player there.
If one player is alone in the sector,
they earn five points.
If 2 players, they each earn 2 points.
If 3 players, they each earn 1 point.
There's 1 comet from Sectors 1 to 8.
If so, there must be two...
in Sectors 10, 12, 14, or 16.
Why don't two of us split up?
- Okay, I'm in.
- Yes.
I'll go to one of the sectors.
If one of you could go...
- to the other sectors.
- Okay.
Your goal in going there is
to keep the other team in check, right?
Yes, keeping the other team in check.
The minute a player goes in there,
they get five points.
It's to prevent that.
Along with that,
you'll go to the twin clouds, right?
Get there,
and the scores will go up together.
- Right.
- That'd be great.
I might even get to the star.
We don't know which letter you are.
How can we know how much you scored?
It'll probably be an odd score.
But you wouldn't know...
if everyone gets even scores
when I get to a star.
Who'd like to set out on a trip with me?
- I'll go backwards.
- Backwards?
Time traveling?
Where will you go?
- I'm thinking of Twelve.
- Twelve?
- Pick one, Keun Woo.
- Sixteen.
Go to two, Hye Seon.
- No, three.
- Yes, three. Two doesn't seem right.
- I'll go to five.
- The round ends...
- They might use it.
- in ten minutes.
Here's what's on my mind.
I think the key is
whether the other team...
puts a black hole
where the twin clouds are.
If it were me,
I'd definitely put it there.
- If I were in that team.
- I wouldn't.
That team is super smart.
They would've expected us to figure out...
where the twin clouds are
with just three questions.
I'm sure they set up a black hole.
What do you think?
Luck plays a bigger role...
- in this game than we think.
- The variables are countless.
What we could do
to make them come in last for sure...
- is to use the black holes.
- Correct.
That team only has
three members' worth of coins.
They would use the black hole
only when necessary,
not from the very beginning.
If so, we should take this chance
to use the black hole...
and make them lose points.
Is it best to move the black hole
starting in Round One?
- Yes.
- Right?
As they don't have enough coins,
that team might not move the black hole...
- in Round One.
- True.
The only ways to get five points are...
- to be alone in a comet...
- Yes.
- or get to a star, right?
We need to block them
from getting to a comet.
- Right.
- Yes.
Locating that comet
won't be easy for them.
Send the black hole to Sectors 6, 7, or 8,
- and they won't get the comet.
- Sectors 6, 7, or 8.
Sectors 6, 7, or 8 sound good.
- Sectors 6, 7, or 8?
- Yes.
We're in Sectors 3, 4, and 5.
Move the black hole to Seven.
Use 6 coins and move the black hole to 7.
Move to 7,
and it'll explode in Sectors 6, 7, or 8.
How may I help you?
I want to choose a location.
Which sector would you like to move to?
I'll move to Sector Four.
You've chosen Sector Four.
- Correct?
- Yes.
(Sector relocation: Sector 4)
I'd like to move another one.
How may I help you?
Please move the black hole
to Sector Seven.
How many coins would you like to bid?
Six coins to Sector Seven, please.
(Black hole: 6 coins, Sector 7)
(Bidding on the black hole)
Two, please.
Sector Three, please.
I'd like to move to Sector 16.
Five.
Sector 12, please.
I choose Sector Three.
The round ends in five minutes.
We have to go to Sectors 4 and 5 each.
We only have to decide on the last one.
The probabilities of the satellite
being here are 25 and 25.
- Yes.
- True.
(Debating on where to move to,
Sector 3 or Sector 6)
If we had one more member,
we could ask for the satellite position.
Should we use up
our Player Location Check Card?
All 3 by using 10,000 dollars?
That's one way.
Should we use all three in order...
as soon as Round Two begins?
I think we should use them
on Park Ji Min and Jeong Keun Woo.
- Park Ji Min.
- Jeong Keun Woo.
How come?
We must make that team come in last place.
Knowing where our targets are...
is important.
Wouldn't they be most likely to come in...
last place?
True, okay.
From that team's perspective,
- that could be it.
- The round ends...
in one minute.
Register...
Please come if you haven't chosen
a location.
Let's try coming in first place.
I can't hold back anymore.
Okay.
(The Minority Alliance begins
to relocate sectors.)
How may I help you?
I'd like to relocate sectors.
Which sector would you like to move to?
(2: Hye Seon, 3: Seong Beom, YunB,
4: Ji Min, 5: Sung Joo, 12: Jin Ho...)
(Kang Ji Hoo chooses Sector 5.)
You've chosen Sector Five.
Correct?
Place me in...
Sector Four.
Which sector would you like to move to?
(4: Kwak Beom, 5: Ji Hoo)
I...
(Will Seung Yong choose Sector 3
or Sector 6?)
Round One has ended.
(Round 1 has ended.)
(Points earned in Round 1)
Here are the results of Round 1.
(Only G got points deducted in Round 1.)
The one who got minus three...
is most likely me.
I will choose Six.
(Seung Yong relocated to Sector 6.)
Even so, we did well.
If we figure out who's where...
after purchasing items in the next round,
we could probably win.
Round 2 will now begin
and run for 30 minutes.
(Round 2 begins.)
Now that it's 7 against 3,
securing items
as soon as Round One ends...
seemed most crucial.
Hi.
How may I help you?
I'd like to use
the Player Location Check Card.
Which player's location
would you like to know?
I choose Jeong Keun Woo.
Jeong Keun Woo was in Sector 16.
When looking at that team,
the key member is probably Team P3.
Team P3 would've...
likely chosen a safe sector.
Teams P1 or P2 would've relocated...
to risky sectors that are hard to observe.
Figuring out where they are
seemed like the best idea.
Thank you.
Park Ji Min was in Sector Four
in the last round.
(Ji Hoo checked Ji Min's location.)
Hyun Sung Joo was in Sector Five
in the last round.
Gosh.
(Minority Alliance's information
on Round 1)
(4: Ji Min, Kwak Beom, twin clouds,
5: Sung Joo, Ji Hoo, twin clouds,)
(6: Seung Yong, 16: Keun Woo)
All right.
- Let's go through them 1 by 1.
- Okay.
- The other team lost three points, right?
- It's Seung Yong.
- Am I right?
- Yes.
We were able to figure out...
that Seung Yong was in Sector Six.
I'd like to know
Player Shin Seung Yong's location.
Shin Seung Yong was in Sector Six
in the last round.
The only score
that was flipped by the black hole...
was the letter G.
And so,
we realized letter G was Seung Yong.
From what I see,
we chose Sector 12 and 16, right?
One of the comets is in here.
So one of A and E must be Keun Woo or me.
That's how we got these points.
Kwak Beom was in Sector Four
in the last round.
The only celestial objects
that can give you two points...
are the comet and the twin clouds.
Since there are 2 twin clouds
among Sectors 3, 4, and 5,
if the two points came from a twin cloud,
at least 3 players would have had
to score 2 points.
Therefore, one can infer that...
the sector worth two points was the comet.
(Comets: 3, only in even-numbered sectors)
Several players earned 3 points
because 5 players chose...
either the satellite or the comet,
- and the points were split among them.
- Exactly.
It's most likely the satellite.
We just have to ask.
There's no need to think about it.
- We...
- Who has the most coins right now?
You, right?
Ask how many satellites there are...
from Sectors 4 to 10.
How many satellites are there
from Sectors 4 to 10?
One?
That means the satellite is
in Sector Three.
The satellite is in Sector Three.
Hye Seon used a coin to ask a question.
We figured out
that there was one satellite...
and pinpointed the twin clouds
in Sectors 4 and 5...
and the satellite
in Sectors 3 for the 1st time.
Sectors 2, 3, 4, 5, and 6 are...
comet, satellite, twin clouds,
twin clouds, and satellite in order.
We've got the celestial objects
for Sectors 2, 3, 4, and 5.
Then there might be 1 dwarf planet
and 1 cosmic dust in Sectors 7 and 8.
No, they could be planets.
Sectors 1, 7, and 8 are a planet,
a dwarf planet, and cosmic dust.
Do we need to get a planet?
Who's next?
- Who didn't ask a question?
- Me.
Go and ask about Sectors 3 to 10.
- Comet.
- Comets in Sectors 3 to 10?
Yes, comets in Sectors 3 to 10.
How many comets are there
from Sectors 3 to 10?
There are 0 comets from Sectors 3 to 10.
Thank you.
Wait. Listen.
Then the comet is definitely in 14.
- Yes, you're right.
- It's in 14.
How may I help you?
Is there a planet in Sectors 3 to 10?
Is there a dwarf planet
in Sectors 3 to 10?
There is 1 dwarf planet
from Sectors 3 to 10.
Got it.
- There is one planet.
- Okay.
- One?
- Add them up and...
There's 1 in Sectors 3 to 10.
- The planet isn't in Sector One.
- No.
- It's not.
- Exactly.
From 3 to 10.
(Majority Alliance's
celestial object information)
Checking out Keun Woo's location
was a great idea.
- For real.
- Yes.
The players who went
to where the twin clouds were...
earned three points.
Only 2 twin clouds exist
in Sectors 1 to 8.
The player
who was in one of Sectors 9 to 16...
must've gotten the other twin cloud.
(The Minority Alliance checked
Jeong Keun Woo's location, Sector 16.)
One of them was Sector 16,
where Keun Woo was.
We were almost certain that...
the twin cloud was in Sector 16.
The comet is likely in Sector Two.
- What do you think?
- Sector Two...
How come?
Two people have two points.
Where you can get two points is...
(4: Twin clouds, 5: Twin clouds,
16: Twin clouds might exist.)
It's not twin clouds,
so it can only be the comet.
You're right. It can only be that.
Observing Round One,
the two who came in last...
might not come from our team
if we put a bit more effort.
Work hard, and we might overcome it.
That was what I thought.
Then...
Let's ask about the dwarf planet.
There are two dwarf planets in total,
and they are not adjacent to a star.
Players lose two points
if they remain in a dwarf planet sector.
(Dwarf planet:
2, neither is adjacent to a star)
Where you definitely lose points is
where the dwarf planet is.
Figuring out where
the dwarf planet is fast seemed important,
so we asked many questions to find it.
(Observation: Dwarf planet)
There is one dwarf planet.
Thank you.
There is 1 dwarf planet in Sectors 3 to 7.
There are 2 satellites in Sectors 3 to 10.
(Celestial object information)
(Majority Alliance)
(Minority Alliance)
Where do we relocate to?
The other team must've used two...
- Player Location Check Cards...
- Yes?
and found out we were in the twin clouds.
- Twin clouds?
- They would've found out...
the twin clouds are in Sectors 4, 5, or 6.
They'll probably move the black hole
to Sector Five.
- After going around once?
- Yes.
The other team will surely find out...
that our teammates are trying
to score points...
by finding out two twin clouds
and the satellite nearby.
The simplest and most straightforward
strategy the other team could play is...
to send the black hole to that area.
By doing so, all of our teammates...
in the twin clouds and satellite
would lose points.
But...
Sectors 4 and 5 are crowded with players.
Correct.
Isn't it best to be among them?
Will they all run away?
I took it further.
Wouldn't they think we'd go
for that straightforward strategy...
and send it somewhere else instead?
The probability was 50-50.
I ended up choosing to save my coins
and stay there.
(Sector relocation: Sector 5)
- How may I help you?
- I'd like to move to Six.
You've been relocated to Sector Six.
- Please head to the main hall.
- Thank you.
What is it? You wanted to talk, right?
Hold on. Those who asked earlier.
Keun Woo.
There's a planet
in Sectors 3 to 10, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Did you ask about the dwarf planet?
- One.
- What?
- There's 1 in Sectors 3 to 10.
- Okay, 1.
When you checked,
- the dwarf planet was in Seven, right?
- Yes.
(Jin Ho checked if the dwarf planet was
in Sectors 3 to 7.)
There is 1 dwarf planet in Sectors 3 to 7.
Got it.
Look.
Sector 1 is cosmic dust,
and Sector 8 is a planet.
I asked just now.
My question was how many cosmic dusts
there were from 3 to 10.
She said two.
- Nine and ten are both cosmic dusts.
- You're right.
(The Majority Alliance
successfully pinpointed...)
(all objects aside from 5 sectors.)
The other team has
double the information...
that we have.
Technically speaking,
it's more than double.
That team must've figured out
the whole celestial object.
The observation of Round Two
has just ended.
The number of questions
both teams asked...
is 14 to 6.
We're totally lost.
Once they figure out the objects,
the members would go to different sectors
and find their scores out.
You can literally go anywhere.
Yes, by using many coins.
I want to go to Two
to check out the comet.
We need such a move. What's good
about playing it conservatively?
It's just slowing us down.
Beom...
wanted to go explore.
We shouldn't be playing this game
conservatively.
If we don't have enough information,
we should use our coins...
and make a move from behind.
If we go too slow
and the score gap gets too big,
it'll be over before we know it.
(Kwak Beom, who wants to explore,
enters the Voting Room.)
How may I help you?
As for me...
I'd like to relocate.
Which sector would you like to move to?
Two, please.
You've been relocated...
- to Sector Two.
- Great.
Please head to the main hall.
(Exploring for the comet)
Round Two has ended.
The 2nd hint will be revealed
for the next 1 minute.
At least one dwarf planet
is adjacent to a planet.
(At least 1 dwarf planet
is adjacent to a planet.)
Here are the results of Round Two.
(Points earned in Round 2)
(Points earned, total score)
Round 3 will now begin
and run for 30 minutes.
The black hole was moved to Five?
That's a big move.
(Majority Alliance's black hole
strategy meeting during Round 2)
Because the other team earned points,
they might maintain their strategy.
We will drop the bomb
in Sectors 4, 5, or 6 just like before.
Look.
The black hole is in Seven right now.
- It's in 8.
- In 8, right?
We'd have to use a bunch of coins
to get it over here from Eight.
Can't one person bet on the black hole
multiple times?
- Like the Mute Card.
- True.
Let's say we have 35 coins.
We could send the black hole 2 to 3 times.
Since the other team has no information,
I'm sure the orders are Kwak Beom, Ji Hoo,
and then Seung Yong.
- I want to crush them.
- You do?
Hyun Sung Joo,
you have submitted 13 coins.
(Relocated the black hole to Sector 5)
I shouldn't have gotten too far ahead.
Luckily, I remained in that location.
So I was the only one
who got caught by it,
and the other two had already fled.
That was a relief.
(Ji Min enters the Voting Room.)
How may I help you?
I'd like to ask a question.
Is the twin cloud anywhere
between Sectors 5 and 12?
(Black hole: Twin clouds)
There's 1 pair of twin clouds
in Sectors 5 to 12.
- There's 1 pair of it in Sectors 5 to 12?
- Yes.
That means it's in Five.
It's 15 and 16.
The clues fell into place
one after the other.
Looking at the celestial objects,
we got most of the locations.
We simply had to figure out
who went to which sector...
as quickly as possible.
Calculate your score
and tell me which sector you were in,
as well as what you would've needed
in this round.
I'm letter E for sure.
Sung Joo and Ji Min are probably
B and I, respectively.
We moved to the satellite
and scored three points.
Three points? That makes sense.
He's on a comet,
and someone else landed on a comet,
so you couldn't score points.
Then I'm likely 1 of these 2.
I'm probably on twin clouds. Sector 16.
Does that mean only you scored?
I got one point.
Nobody was on Sectors 4 and 5
for twin clouds.
That's how I got the points by myself.
I don't know
where the remaining one point came from.
- Keun Woo and YunB...
- You're right.
shared the comet score. Two points each.
(The Majority Alliance deduced
many alphabets.)
(Jin Ho, Ji Min or Sung Joo,
YunB or Keun Woo, Hye Seon,)
(Ji Hoo or Kwak Beom, Seung Yong,
Ji Min or Sung Joo, Seong Beom)
How did he score one point?
- Seung Yong?
- Yes.
(Majority Alliance deduced G
to be Seung Yong.)
G, one point.
How did this happen?
Seung Yong could've moved
to either Sector 5 or Sector 7.
Sector 7 is minus 2,
but that wasn't his score.
He can't have been in Sector 7.
- Exactly.
- Four or five.
He must've jumped.
He neither went here nor there.
Where did he go to?
Maybe this isn't Seung Yong.
What are the ways
for 2 people to score 1 point?
Two people in the same twin clouds sector.
It makes sense if two people were...
in the same twin clouds sector.
Someone else came to your sector.
He jumped that much?
- That's why I said it didn't make sense.
- That doesn't make sense.
But that's the only explanation.
(10 minutes ago)
I'll relocate the sector.
Which sector would you like to move to?
Sector 16.
If we stay in the same sector,
we cannot learn new information.
Since Seung Yong already had
a lot of points deducted,
we decided to send him
to another side to explore...
the uncharted territory.
Which means Seung Yong was
in Sector 16 this round.
From 6 to 16.
Who hasn't asked a question yet?
- Have you?
- Not yet.
Then go...
and ask about dwarf planets
between Sectors 5 and 11.
Sectors 5 to 11, dwarf planet.
How many dwarf planets are there
from Sectors 5 to 11?
- So?
- Two.
- Two? Got them.
- Right.
(2 dwarf planets)
By the time we asked 1 to 2 questions
in the beginning of Round 3,
we identified the 16 sectors...
of Project Galaxy,
the most important part of the game.
(They've identified every celestial object
except the star in 3 rounds.)
Did they go to cosmic dust
to get zero points?
- That's possible.
- Definitely.
They are...
(Cosmic dust, no change in scores)
searching for the star as well.
Figuring out the star's location
as soon as possible...
before the opponents do...
and moving the black hole there...
to give them minus five points...
could turn the tables.
We need to find the star quickly.
The moment we find the star,
we'll all go to the sector with it.
Then the game ends.
- The star isn't here.
- Definitely not.
- Why not Sector 1?
- Because I got 0 points.
She was here, and she got zero points.
We need to send YunB on a business trip.
You need to go to Sector 13,
the one nearby.
How may I help you?
I'll relocate to Sector 13.
(YunB goes on a journey to find the star.)
I'll keep going as is.
You've chosen Sector 13.
Should I go to 15 this time?
You're going to 15? Then I'll go to 16.
Then I'll go to 16.
I'll just go to 15.
I didn't check that.
Round 3 ends in 5 minutes.
There are so many things to do
for this game.
How may I help you?
I'll relocate to Sector 15.
I'll relocate to Sector 16.
How may I help you?
I'll relocate.
I'll relocate to Sector 14.
They might move the black hole,
don't you think?
- Right.
- Yes.
They'll aim for the twin clouds, right?
The twins?
Don't you think
they'll aim for the twin clouds?
- Here?
- Sectors 15 and 16.
Will they attack this?
Should we...
Is it time for us to gamble here?
Should we bet on the black hole?
But it's too early to use it.
No.
Using it now to stir them up
could be a way.
But we have seven more rounds left.
If we move the back hole now
by placing a bet,
we can't do it anymore later.
I'm torn.
I can't decide which move to make.
It was a really crucial moment.
We had the same scores as them
in Round One,
and we were slightly behind in Round Two.
If we played our cards right
in Round Three,
we could win.
Here are the results of Round 3.
(Points earned in Round 3)
(Points earned, total score)
Round 4 will now begin
and run for 30 minutes.
(Points earned in Round 3)
(F and H, minus 5)
(Surprised)
There are 2 minus 5?
We expected it could be possible
to get minus 2 or 3 points...
after the attack.
And out of nowhere, we got minus 5.
What happened?
I was...
so confused when I saw it.
Why did we get minus five?
That's only possible
if they were in the star sector...
and got black holed.
Minus five happens...
when the initial 5 points turn
into minus 5 points...
due to the black hole's effect.
You can score five points
on the comet and the star.
(Comet)
But only one person is allowed
in the sectors with comets...
to be able to score five points
to themselves.
Which means there cannot be
multiple five-point scorers.
(Comet)
How come there are 2 minus 5 scorers?
The only way to score five...
is staying in a comet by yourself, right?
This doesn't make sense.
(You can't have multiple 5-point scorers
with a comet.)
So that's the star, not a comet.
How did the five points come about?
(Majority Alliance gathers
in the pantry quickly.)
The black hole is the only thing...
- that can result in minus five.
- Right.
But that doesn't make sense...
because 3 people can't score 5 points.
You score from a comet
if you're on a comet alone.
What if, by sheer luck,
all three of them were on the star?
Or we got the whole thing wrong.
It's one or the other.
There's only one possibility,
going by the rule.
If we move the black hole
to the sector with the star,
plus 5 will reverse to become minus 5.
(Jin Ho checks the black hole's location
for Round 3.)
They wouldn't know where the star is...
when even we don't know yet.
We know where the black hole is,
and there's no star there.
So it's not that case.
Gosh, what's happening?
Why doesn't it make sense?
The black hole...
The star didn't explode
from the black hole.
That's right.
(No matter what scores they plug in,
they get an error.)
I had a mental breakdown.
We might've gotten
the whole planisphere wrong.
If we'd calculated wrongly from the start,
where do we need to restart from?
It was so daunting.
If we need to redo the whole thing,
where did we get it wrong?
I might've missed a spy.
We might have a rat among us.
They got really confused because of us.
(10 minutes ago)
Since we mostly figured it out...
It all comes down to placing bets
in the later rounds.
Yes.
Let's go.
How many coins do you have left?
Or would it be better
for you to relocate the black hole?
I can do that. Where to?
How many coins did you use?
I used quite a lot. Wait, I didn't.
- You used four.
- Yes.
I queued up after the round ended,
so I can't enter. That's what she said.
Kang Ji Hoo.
You've queued up after the round ended,
so you may not enter.
She said the time was up.
So there was nothing I could do.
- But we were in line here.
- Yes.
Is it because I went down
to fetch the note?
Wait.
I have a question.
Does lining up behind Seong Beom
not count?
You have lined up
after the announcement...
that the round has ended.
(1 minute before Round 3 ended)
Round 3 ends in 1 minute.
This.
What's that?
Shall we move to Sector 13?
- Sounds like a plan.
- I'll go here.
I'll relocate the black hole to Sector 15.
(Glancing)
We should bet on both...
Yes.
We still have enough coins.
We should try and gamble.
We must try what we can in this round.
- Good idea.
- Round Three has ended.
That sounds like a good idea.
So two of us will go to Sector 3?
(Minority Alliance did not relocate
to another sector.)
- Both of you?
- Yes.
Do you want to go
to the same or different sector?
Let's line up.
Shall we?
We were discussing
the locations of the stars...
and the sector relocations.
We were too focused...
that we missed the announcement.
So we couldn't relocate.
(Minority Alliance has exceeded
the time limit.)
"There must be a mistake."
That was what I thought at first.
When I found out that wasn't the case,
I realized I'd made a mistake.
We were definitely lined up.
Did we line up after the time was up?
We were confused.
It felt like the sky was falling.
I was so upset.
We can't relocate either.
We can't enter the room at all.
We can't take any action.
Darn it.
It'll be minus five for us.
If we can't move.
That's a rule?
"If you do not relocate to
a different sector before the round ends,"
"five points will be deducted
from the round's points."
I'm sorry. We're stuck.
We messed up badly.
We didn't queue up.
I checked the rule book,
and it was minus five points.
It's hard to get just one point,
but minus five?
Pretend that we relocated.
Pretend.
- Okay.
- Pretend that we relocated.
We have no other choice.
This is how we'll shake them up.
We need to make them think,
"How did they get minus five
when they relocated?"
We hardened our resolves.
"We can do it." We couldn't give up.
Let's stay mentally strong.
The other team must be confused too.
Let's not show how upset we are.
They can see we got minus five,
but they don't know why.
We must never let it show
that we couldn't go in.
Let's pretend that we landed on the star
and got hit by the black hole.
That means I'm H.
We can use the black hole
in the next round.
You can go on a challenge without worries.
(Minority Alliance
discusses enthusiastically.)
We need to find out the exact location
of the star and everything.
(Round 4, total score)
(Comet, satellite, twin clouds, satellite,
dwarf planet, planet, comet, twin clouds)
What do we still not know?
- Dwarf planet.
- Okay.
Dwarf planet, star,
- cosmic dust.
- Cosmic dust.
("Dwarf planet is not adjacent
to a star.")
Sector 14 is...
(Using this rule,
you can specify the star's location.)
All we can do is ask for the dwarf planet.
Will you go and ask?
Four are cosmic dusts
and one is a dwarf planet, right?
Yes.
We haven't found the star yet,
so if we find it
at least a round before the opponents,
we could make up for the loss.
I thought we should do our best
to find the star...
in the next round.
From Sectors 7 to 14,
how many dwarf planets are there?
There are 2 dwarf planets
from Sectors 7 to 14.
There are two dwarf planets.
(Dwarf planet, planet, comet)
Sector One is cosmic dust, confirmed.
(Sector 1, cosmic dust)
Hello.
How many dwarf planets are there
from Sectors 10 to 14?
There is 1 dwarf planet
from Sectors 10 to 14.
(Observation: Dwarf planet, 1)
One.
This is confirmed as cosmic dust.
(Sector 9, cosmic dust)
A dwarf planet from Sectors 10 to 14.
What question should I ask?
Why don't we...
Yes, make it less.
To check smaller sectors,
- you need to use more coins.
- Use them.
And I'll buy more coins.
Think about a risky move.
What risky move should we make?
I have 15 coins left.
Should I make a risky move this round?
Shall we just stand there and talk,
just to be safe?
Okay.
That sounds about right.
This is our turf now.
Goodness.
- That was terrible.
- I agree.
- Let's discuss here.
- Okay.
(They moved to a cozier meeting space.)
How many dwarf planets are there
from Sectors 7 to 10?
There is 1 dwarf planet
from Sectors 7 to 10.
Darn it.
(Observation: Dwarf planet, 1)
I'll buy coins.
- Would you like to purchase coins?
- Yes.
You get five coins.
(He purchased a 5-coin item
at 10,000 dollars.)
(The dwarf planet candidates
and the star candidates...)
(were narrowed down
with the observations.)
It...
Hi.
I bought coins, so I have 25 now.
You have 25? Let's discuss here.
To prevent any mishap,
we'll stand in the queue.
We need to plan our next move.
Do you think...
they'll relocate the black hole
to the star?
(Round 4, total score)
In this round? I think they will.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Cosmic dust, comet, satellite,
twin clouds, satellite, dwarf planet...)
I didn't use any coin, so I have 30.
This is the round to find the star.
I think they'll relocate the black hole
to the star,
thinking we've figured out
where the star is.
We'll find out where the star is
after checking their move...
and earn even small points.
(They plan to find the star
with the location of the black hole.)
Why don't we try that?
- Earn small points?
- Yes.
Because no matter what they do,
they'll assume we've found the star.
- We?
- Yes.
Since we're not sure yet,
- we won't...
- Yes.
- bet on the black hole.
- We'll earn small points.
- Okay.
We'll play safe for this round.
- Where should we go?
- The twin clouds.
(They relocate to the twin clouds,
which secure them small but safe points.)
I'll relocate to another sector.
(Sector relocation: Sector 16)
I'll move to Sector 15.
- Hello.
- How may I help you?
I'll move to Sector Five.
(Sector relocation: Sector 6 to Sector 5)
Which sector would you like to move to?
Sector 15.
You've been relocated to Sector 15.
(Sector relocation: Sector 2 to Sector 15)
Thank you.
- The round ends in five minutes.
- Don't be panicked.
We need to do this.
- Let's go and queue up.
- Yes.
Take it with you.
- I'm back.
- How may I help you?
I'll relocate...
by using coins.
I'll relocate.
I'll relocate to another sector.
(All players have been relocated.)
Round Four has ended.
The 3rd hint will be revealed
for the next 1 minute.
(All comets are adjacent to cosmic dust.)
All comets are adjacent to cosmic dust.
(Cosmic dust in Sector 1,
cosmic dust in Sector 13)
This is the cosmic dust.
(They identified the cosmic dust
next to a comet...)
(and the last dwarf planet from the hint.)
Here are the results of the last round.
(Points earned in Round 4)
(Points earned, total score)
Round 5 will now begin
and run for 30 minutes.
(Points earned in Round 4)
They found the star.
(Round 5, total score)
(Points earned in Round 4)
(Majority Alliance had
multiple 5-point scorers.)
Why did Ji Hoo score minus two?
(Sector 5, Ji Hoo)
Because of the black hole.
(Sector 4, Black hole)
You went that way?
I think we're blocked off by the comets.
Right?
(D and J, who scored 2 points,
probably went to comets.)
(Ji Hoo, minus 2, Seung Yong, 2,
Kwak Beom, 2)
(D and J, who scored 2 points,
probably went to comets.)
I saw their scores in Round Four,
and it looked like they'd figured out
all the celestial objects.
Since when have they been playing
so strategically?
We can't beat them.
(Sighing)
Or we got the whole thing wrong.
It's one or the other.
No, we can't be so utterly wrong.
I snapped out of it.
If we waver mentally,
it will lead to a loss of manpower.
This is you, right?
- I think it's me. Twin clouds.
- Okay.
That means I'm J.
YunB.
- Keun Woo.
- This?
Don't you think...
they're F, G, and H?
They're F, G, and H.
(They identified the opponents' letters
by rechecking.)
We found out
when we were calculating the scores.
Those three letters in a row belong
to the other team.
I think...
They queued up a bit late behind me.
They might have been denied entry.
- That can't be.
- So they moved just one sector?
No. They couldn't move at all,
so they scored minus five.
What's this?
Could they really have...
gotten the penalty because they failed
to enter within the time limit?
It's so unrealistic.
Who would make that kind of mistake here?
What if it's a trick?
All the other scores except theirs
are correct.
I think they just couldn't enter.
Could they have made use of it?
They weren't even trying to trick us.
They just failed to enter the room.
They were too stunned.
Let's not get flustered.
- Right.
- Focus on our tasks.
We don't have much time.
But that unrealistic situation
became real.
Tripping on their own foot
and falling down...
is the worst possible situation
that can happen.
(Points earned in Round 3)
I think I'm D.
Hey.
(Cosmic dust or star)
(YunB had moved
to the potential star sector in Round 3.)
You didn't get any score, so you're C.
- You're C.
- That's right.
(Round 5, total score)
That means Sector 13 is cosmic dust.
We found the star.
- Nice! The best...
- Yes.
This is the best scenario.
We had two star candidates.
The explorers went on an expedition,
and they managed to avoid the star.
The remaining cosmic dust
was identified as the star.
We figured out the star's location
from Round Four.
Everyone go to that sector
in the next round.
But we can't all stay there...
because we need to move at least
one sector in the following round.
So we came up with a plan.
Half will go to the star,
and the other half will defend
the satellites and the twin clouds.
Then we'll switch it up,
so the defenders go to the star...
and those on the star go to defend.
(They'll prevent Minority Alliance
from scoring and score on the star.)
This is the strategy of Majority Alliance.
The players need to move...
one sector or more forward for each round.
So they'll split up the alliance into two.
One group will score on the star sector,
and the other group will prevent
Minority Alliance from scoring.
Using this strategy,
Majority Alliance can
steadily earn points...
and interfere with Minority Alliance
at the same time.
To widen the score gap,
we split up into two.
We prevented Minority Alliance
from scoring a lot from the comets...
or from the satellites or the planets.
We went into defense mode.
(Stopping Minority Alliance
while scoring themselves)
Who has lower scores now?
- Raise your hand.
- Me.
(Jin Ho, YunB, and Hye Seon
have the lowest scores.)
- I'm 4.
- You 3 should go.
I'll move to Sector 9.
I'll move from Sector 2 to Sector 9.
Look.
- You're in Sector 15, right?
- Yes.
- Go to Sector 14.
- What about you?
- I'll go to Sector 12.
- Okay.
I'll move to Sector 14.
I'll relocate to Sector 12.
You both go to Sector Six.
Go to Sector Six and take the satellite.
Go to Sector Six?
We'll move the black hole
to somewhere else.
So you'll get three points each.
I'll move from Sector 8 to Sector 6.
The other team doesn't have
much information,
so they'll be psychologically drawn to...
where they'd scored.
We'll read their steps ahead...
and send the black hole to them.
They come to earn points...
and leave with minus points.
Ji Min and Sung Joo moved
to a satellite...
and prevented Minority Alliance
from scoring on the planet.
Seong Beom and Keun Woo moved to comets...
to stop Minority Alliance
from monopolizing the comets.
Lastly, they relocated the black hole
to the twin clouds.
A meticulous plan was executed.
(Seong Beom reviews the strategy
for Round 5.)
It really works in our favor...
that the planet is adjacent to the star.
Everyone on the star
will move to the planet,
and the rest can gather at the star.
One person has to defend the comet.
So I think Jin Ho or Hye Seon...
could go to the comet...
and try to earn five points...
since they're not in contention anyway.
Anything is fine.
Are you okay with Sector 12? The comet?
- I'm fine with anywhere.
- Okay.
We still haven't figured out...
a few letters,
but even compared
with the lowest total scorer on my team,
we're still leading with a wide gap.
We're safe.
I started to feel more relaxed then.
The situation...
It's over.
It's over. There was no variable.
There's no variable.
Isn't the game over, to be honest?
I'm set to be in last place.
- Yes.
- I'm the one in last place.
- You scored more minus points than me.
- Right.
I'm minus 7, you're minus 3.
Among Sectors 9 and 10,
which one is the star?
(Sectors 9 and 10: Cosmic dust)
Only if we could find out.
(Minority Alliance
hasn't found the star yet.)
To double-check, I'll ask...
how many cosmic dusts there are.
To check if we got it right?
We have nothing else to ask.
I'll go and ask.
How many cosmic dusts there are?
(Minority Alliance has found
all the celestial objects sans the star.)
There's nothing to ask.
How may I help you?
How many cosmic dusts are there
from Sectors 9 to 16?
There are three cosmic dusts...
from Sectors 9 to 16.
We're right.
I wanted to double-check just in case.
- This is iffy.
- What should we do?
(They're 8 to 15 points behind Jin Ho,)
(who has the lowest score
in the other team.)
If we'd kept going...
without missing
that one sector relocation,
even with just three people,
we could attack them once or twice.
Before that round, I told myself...
I'd fight until the end.
It felt like I was forfeited
the chance to turn the tables...
with my own mistake.
So I felt a lot more helpless.
We did our best until Round Four.
But the score gap increased so much...
that we couldn't catch up.
The game is as good as finished.
The opponents decide
where the black hole goes too.
I've already scored minus five,
so there was no way I could win.
The more we played,
the deeper we dug our grave.
Ji Hoo must've finished his calculation.
He would've known in his head.
We can't...
win this game.
We've started...
to accept defeat.
I don't think
they'll relocate the black hole...
to where the star is.
We're locked into last places.
Last place has been decided.
No matter how much we struggle,
we can't catch up.
They've divided themselves into groups.
"You go here."
"I went here. You scored this much,
and I scored this much."
That's what they're doing.
Yes.
We can try to go to certain sectors...
and get 2 scores instead of 3,
but nothing will change.
They made the game so boring.
We now need to... Seung Yong.
We'll just score minuscule points...
and go for the Deathmatch.
It's meaningless.
When Round Four ends,
it's impossible for us to win,
no matter how we calculate.
We couldn't identify
all the celestial objects until then.
We'll be splitting...
and sharing...
the small points.
"You score five points this time."
"I'll score 1. I'll score 3."
You take it.
Losers.
Sung Joo must've known yesterday.
- That was him distancing himself from us.
- What?
He was distancing himself from us.
We did have a talk yesterday.
I didn't know.
He suddenly moved his things out.
"Team P2 needs to sleep together."
I think that was also a lie.
All the puzzle pieces...
It feels like
Hye Seon's laugh is fake too.
Since when did they start to plot?
"Let's kill Seung Yong."
But they couldn't kill him
in the Mafia Game.
Because killing him would kill them too.
This is the real Killer Game.
I do want to find out...
who started the whole
"Seung Yong is the target" thing.
Who do you think?
I need to play the Deathmatch anyway.
So I want to pick that person.
Ji Min?
No. High chance it's Seong Beom.
Either Seong Beom or Ji Min?
In Round Five,
Project Galaxy was over for us.
We started the Mafia Game
to find out who had instigated this.
When we voted for the Deathmatch
yesterday...
- Yes.
We merely discussed among ourselves,
but since you're
technically our team leader,
you became the target.
- To eliminate me?
- What?
To eliminate me?
Well, you know...
- Should I be honest?
- Yes.
I won't beat around the bush.
They don't like you.
- Who? Seong Beom?
- I don't know.
Someone among them.
They just don't like you.
They talked about the narrative whatnot,
so I told them to quit the nonsense.
What kind of narrative
are you talking about?
They go,
"It's just a game, no hard feelings."
"This was today. Tomorrow we start anew."
They say all that,
but after so many games,
they're talking about the Heist Day.
That's nonsense.
(YunB had told him about
how they were using the Heist Day...)
(to come together.)
Seung Yong now has a giant target
on his back.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Until yesterday,
when someone did something in the game,
they said, "It's just a game."
"It was a game, so it's fine."
But now, because they want to survive,
they came up with a pretext.
They're liars.
They're purely a group of liars.
I rarely get angry.
But I get angry when someone does
something really below the belt.
Can I just check one thing?
Two of us will be playing the Deathmatch.
Whoever first suggested...
to kill Seung Yong,
why don't you proudly go
to the Deathmatch with us?
Don't hide behind the group.
Someone must've suggested it first.
The person who suggested
to kill Shin Seung Yong.
I just wanted to hear it.
"I said it,
and I suggested to kill him..."
"because I didn't like Seung Yong."
Just one sentence,
and everything can be resolved.
I'm offering to make you a ring,
so why won't you fight?
- It's me.
- Don't be... Sorry?
- Let's go, then.
Let's go. I'll play.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Keun Woo.
You keep hiding,
and there's nothing fun about it.
- It's me.
- We never hid it to begin with.
I heard that this group was formed...
because someone had suggested it.
You've played it out nicely...
and killed him off.
- Why don't you fight head-on, man to man?
- Sure. I'll go.
- Then you, Keun Woo?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Let's do this.
When we go to the Deathmatch,
let's bring with us the guy
who suggested...
targeting Seung Yong.
And who is that?
I'm going to find that now.
You'll find...
Keun Woo played a big role.
Thanks to that, I became certain...
that Ji Min had planned this.
You won't go. Don't worry.
They just need to pick...
who they want.
But the fact...
they were trying to deduce it...
I just couldn't understand.
Who suggested killing Seung Yong?
What will they do if they find out?
What will they do if we say it's Jin Ho?
Exactly.
Let's see if they'll do the same
to stronger players.
They think Seung Yong is the common enemy.
He's not even a common enemy.
It's just karma.
He should just accept
that the time has come.
They don't understand that.
They just think...
we didn't play fair today...
- and rounded up on him to kill him.
- What exactly is fair play?
Did we make a mistake? No, they made it.
They just don't understand it.
I didn't get them from the start.
"We're the minority."
"We can't play this game well."
They put on a grumpy face...
from the start until the end.
"I won't play.
It's so disadvantageous for us."
Then go home.
Why are you still here?
But I thought, "Who knows?"
"They could've come up..."
"with a jaw-dropping plan."
I told myself...
I'd secure a perfect win.
Let's go line up.
Remember your sectors?
Let's discuss where to relocate to.
I'll use one and go to Sector 14.
Then I'll go to Sector Ten.
You're going to Sector Ten?
Then...
I'll go to Sector Nine.
Let's line up.
Let's go.
Isn't it better to go together?
(Minority Alliance splits up
and goes to Sectors 9 and 10.)
If we can't find it, that's that.
How may I help you?
I'll move to Sector Ten.
(Shin Seung Yong relocates to Sector 10,
which is either the star or cosmic dust.)
I'll move to Sector Nine.
(Kang Ji Hoo relocates to Sector 9,
which is either the star or cosmic dust.)
I'll move to Sector 14.
(Kwak Beom relocates to Sector 14.)
- You've been relocated to Sector 14.
- Okay.
(The 3 players of Minority Alliance
have relocated.)
How may I help you?
I'll relocate.
I'll move from Sector 6 to Sector 9.
I'll move to Sector Nine.
Sector Nine.
(They move to the sector with the star.)
Choi Hye Seon,
which sector would you like to move to?
I'll move to Sector Eight.
I'll move to Sector 12.
(Jin Ho relocates to defend the comets.)
(Sector relocation: Sector 9 to Sector 12)
Round Five has ended.
Keun Woo, you volunteered...
- for the Deathmatch just now.
- Yes.
- I wasn't here for the Heist Day.
- Right.
This whole alliance is built...
on pretexts.
The fact I wasn't here on the Heist Day...
worked out very well for me.
They can't blame me.
They have no pretext to pick me...
for the Deathmatch.
I'm in a position
where I could control them,
which is fascinating.
Everything falls into place.
Regarding this situation,
those who brought the people together...
using Seung Yong as the common enemy...
were Seung Beom, Ji Min,
and Hye Seon.
When they were forced...
to ally with that team as citizens,
those who had the most conflict
and got most hurt...
were Seong Beom and Hye Seon as well.
(The voting situation the day before)
(Seong Beom and Hye Seon didn't agree
with the others in the winning team.)
- What do you mean?
- We're also part of the winning team,
but they won't even include us
in their conversation.
Going by the pretexts,
Seong Beom, Hye Seon, and Ji Min are
on top of the list.
- That's also true.
- Yes.
But we can't...
- encourage them.
- We can't force them.
In that case, the first place...
There are Seong Beom, Ji Min,
and Hye Seon. The three victims.
If any of them don't win first place,
we have two remaining.
I think it gives them a better pretext...
- if 1 of the 2 plays the Deathmatch.
- Well, that team will decide.
- That's right.
- They'd think similarly.
If they're going to purge,
it'll be best for Ji Min or Seong Beom...
to chop Seung Yong's head off themselves.
When it comes to Bloody Game,
my priority is to survive...
no matter what method I need to use.
Halfway through,
I started to gaslight them...
about the importance of pretexts.
Before Round Six starts,
the hidden item will get revealed now.
The hidden item of Project Galaxy is...
(Black Hole Immunity: Defend once
against the effects of the black hole)
Black Hole Immunity.
Black Hole Immunity...
gives you the ability
to become immune to the black hole.
The user's score will not be reversed...
even if they are affected
by the black hole.
Once purchased,
it will be automatically used...
when you get affected by the black hole.
You can purchase it in the Voting Room
starting now,
and the number of available stock is one.
Buy it.
You understood, right?
How may I help you?
I think Ji Hoo bought Black Hole Immunity.
They might pretend to support Ji Hoo...
and bomb us with the black hole.
They could send Ji Hoo
with Black Hole Immunity...
to the star...
and send the black hole
to the star as well.
The hidden item was Black Hole Immunity.
You might think it's nothing much,
but when you think about it,
the moment five points from the star...
turns into minus five,
the score gap decreases by ten points.
This is huge.
I started to get worried then.
How may I help you?
I'll buy the hidden item.
Heo Seong Beom,
will you purchase Black Hole Immunity?
Was that a question?
Yes, it was.
I entered the Voting Room,
and the item was left for me to purchase.
"What's happening?
Why didn't they buy it?"
I thought...
they'd definitely buy the item.
(5 minutes ago)
How may I help you?
Nothing.
To bide my time, to get my revenge,
I decided to save my money.
We wanted to trick them to show them...
that we haven't completely given up.
I'll buy it.
(Heo Seong Beom purchases
Black Hole Immunity.)
Heo Seong Beom, 20,000 dollars
will be deducted from your funds.
When you're affected by the black hole,
it will automatically activate once.
To prevent the opponents from buying it...
and making an irregular move,
I decided to buy it myself.
I'll buy it
and take away their opportunity.
Here are the results of the last round.
(Points earned in Round 5)
Round 6 will now begin
and run for 30 minutes.
I think F found the star, right?
(F earned 5 points.)
(F is Kang Ji Hoo.)
In Round Five, we found out...
Sectors 9 and 10 were
cosmic dust and a star.
Seung Yong and I went...
to explore one each.
After Round Five ended,
I scored five points.
I could immediately identify Sector Nine
as the star.
One of them would be in last place.
(Beom, Seung Yong, Ji Hoo)
That's right.
We've come a long way.
Yes, we did come a long way.
We started
from the outdoor survival grounds.
We've never met before.
That's right.
Ji Hoo is so reliable.
I'm glad he's with us.
(Nodding)
He's the best ally I found.
I agree.
We grew fond of him.
Ji Hoo is very smart,
so we could rely on him
when playing games.
That was when I decided.
Seung Yong, come here.
Let's save Ji Hoo.
- What?
- Let's save Ji Hoo.
Okay.
Ji Hoo wasn't even on my team.
But because he was seen around me,
he automatically got placed
in Minority Alliance.
So we decided to save Ji Hoo.
Our score difference is only one.
We could enter a satellite together.
I'll move to Sector Six.
(Sector relocation: Sector 9 to Sector 6)
(Shin Seung Yong and Kang Ji Hoo
moved to the same sector.)
You have submitted two coins.
How about this?
I hand over the black hole.
Okay.
- And send it there.
- What?
There.
- That's not so bad.
- We can defend,
- Not bad.
- and we can send Ji Hoo off.
I'll see you later, then.
How may I help you?
You see,
I'll try and move the black hole.
Yes. And I'm going to bet...
(Stopping)
One second.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
I'm so stupid.
I thought I had more coins.
I was so stupid.
I apologize.
Here.
Please state the number of coins
you'd like to bet.
(Seong Beom counts the number of spaces.)
I spent quite a while in there.
That's all right. I just got here.
One thing I've learned
on Bloody Game X was...
that the honest one always loses.
I think Beom just bet on the black hole.
- This time?
- I heard him counting his coins.
I think he spent 8 or 10 coins.
I think he sent it
to where the star blows up.
- In this round?
- Yes.
(Black hole)
The black hole is in Sector Nine.
I'm betting on Sector Nine.
You've bet on the black hole
moving ten spaces.
- Yes.
- That means we can spend...
just over 10 or 11.
- We need 12.
- Okay.
I decided to keep the opposing team...
in check for sure.
How may I help you?
I'll bet on the black hole.
Please state the number of coins
you'd like to bet.
Twelve.
(Black hole, 12 coins)
(Seong Beom spent 12 coins
to bet the black hole in Sector 11.)
It moves to Sector 11.
Once we get through this part,
the game's over.
- Yes, it is.
- Yes.
(Star: YunB, Hye Seon, Jin Ho)
(Comet: Ji Min,
Planet: Sung Joo, Seong Beom, Keun Woo)
Round Six has ended.
(Round 6 has ended.)
Here are the results of the last round.
Please.
What?
(Points earned in Round 6)
(Jin Ho, B, YunB, Keun Woo, Hye Seon,
Ji Hoo, Seung Yong, Beom, I, Seong Beom)
(Except for Ji Min,
who moved to Sector 14,)
(and Seong Beom,
whose Black Hole Immunity was activated,)
(all members of the Majority Alliance
lost points.)
Round 7 will now begin
and run for 30 minutes.
That's good.
Great. That was cool.
I couldn't believe they pulled it off.
It actually worked.
I went in to sacrifice myself.
Please state the number of coins
you'd like to bet.
(He bet 15 coins...)
(on the black hole.)
(Seong Beom miscounted the coins.)
They still have to compete
for first place,
so we'll have to keep an eye on them.
One of them...
might betray them out of nowhere.
I wasn't trying to win.
I wanted to start an internal conflict.
The scores will be different
from their plan,
and one of them will want more points
and betray them.
(Ji Min is now the sole leader.)
(Sung Joo was tied for 1st place,
and now he's 3rd.)
I was naturally headed toward first place.
I thought, "I won."
I was tied for first place,
and I got incredibly unlucky.
That one...
might have been a naive judgment.
While spending 12 coins
to move the black hole,
I doubted they spent more than that.
But they did, in fact.
Round Six's results were announced.
Ji Hoo and Jin Ho's scores were...
only seven points apart.
So, I realized we were in a crisis.
The things we were worried about
did happen.
I had to play three times harder
from then on.
I went in to sacrifice myself.
Why would you follow me?
It's dangerous.
Those guys are so weird.
And I'll relocate to Sector Nine.
(He moved to Sector 9
where the black hole was.)
You have relocated to Sector Nine.
There was only one score
you could actually control.
Going down the ranks.
It's hard to climb up,
but it's easy to go down.
Who are you going to pick?
Let's say you and I are going
to the Deathmatch.
- Yes.
- And they have...
- an elimination immunity pass.
- Yes.
I think they'll give it to the one
who we might choose.
- Yes.
- They'll give them one.
I doubt they'll give it to Seong Beom.
Why? Because he's in first place?
No, because they think...
he'll win the Deathmatch.
I think they'll give it to Ji Min.
What should we do?
Who are your top three picks?
Me?
Seong Beom, Ji Min, and Sung Joo.
My list is pretty similar.
We'll see who gets the pass
and who places first.
Seong Beom might place first,
- and Ji Min might get the pass.
- Yes.
Then, we'll need to pick one more
other than Sung Joo.
Your fourth pick.
- Sung Joo and Jin Ho.
- Jin Ho?
Who else is there?
Sung Joo, let's at least have a talk.
It's like you're trying
to cut ties with us.
You're not going to talk to us at all?
Were you promised an immunity pass?
No.
Wasn't that the reason you joined them?
I was going to ask at first,
but I decided not to.
I knew they wouldn't say yes.
- Then, why did you join them?
- Why did you leave?
- I just...
- We're going to take you down with us.
You wanted to win?
You're lying, right?
Are you being for real?
- Of course, we are.
- Of course.
Who's the other one?
You're our only target.
They'll ask you to pick two.
You'll only pick me...
- so that they can't vote?
- Yes.
Just tell us...
if they're trying to put Ji Min
in the first place.
All the other information...
- The two of us will surely place last.
- Yes.
- The least you can do is tell us that.
- Well...
We had an agreement,
so I won't be doing that.
- But...
- What was the agreement?
Just tell us that.
We haven't decided on anything yet.
We won't pick you if you tell us that.
What do you say?
Who do they want to put in first place?
Yes, their plan.
We know we're going to lose.
I'll need to see how it goes.
They haven't decided on it yet.
They haven't?
If...
this offer works for you,
feel free to tell us.
No.
(Wandering around)
(Round 7, total score)
(Jin Ho, Ji Min, YunB,
Keun Woo, Hye Seon,)
(Ji Hoo, Seung Yong, Beom,
Sung Joo, Seong Beom)
Smoke break?
Oh, man.
I feel like you're just having fun...
- because you're bored.
- No, I'm not.
I just like you.
But I just want to tell you this.
We have...
already decided
on who'll go to the Deathmatch.
- Ji Hoo and I are tied,
- Yes.
so I just bet on the black hole
and went with it.
- I have one thing to tell you.
- Okay.
The last two players have to choose...
- the candidates.
- Right.
Say Seong Beom places first,
and he gives the immunity pass
to Ji Min or Hye Seon.
Then, the other one is
the only justified choice...
for this narrative to be persuasive.
Justification and narrative are
all important,
but this team has the right
to make the choice.
We just want some information...
- because we heard about the narrative...
- Yes.
- from YunB about why the team...
- Right.
- was divided in the first place.
- Yes.
That's how they formed a team.
- So, you can at least tell us that.
- Yes, I understand.
That way, we know
how the narrative started,
- which was because of Seung Yong.
- Yes.
There were victims
due to Seung Yong's actions,
- which divided the team,
- Yes.
- and it led to this Deathmatch.
So, we just want to know
what we're missing...
along the process.
We have the narrative,
and we have a justification...
to eliminate Seung Yong, right?
That's been building up until now.
And then, Xitsuh...
and Tae Gyun had to leave.
That's what you're missing.
Because those two meant so much to us.
So, that was the middle point.
Right. The only one.
- Yes, I understand it all.
- Yes.
You were all talking
about narratives and justifications,
so I wanted to know
what the justification for today was.
Today,
other than the heist...
- I want to know who insisted on that.
- Yesterday's...
I have to know that
before I pick one for the Deathmatch.
- It's not that someone insisted.
- I can't just pick anyone.
Each team lost a teammate yesterday,
and everyone simultaneously felt that.
They were like, "We're going
to eliminate Seung Yong tomorrow."
- It's not...
- That's why I know it was Ji Min.
- Yes, you're right.
- Ji Min.
But she...
He said, "I don't care, YunB.
Just tell me."
"Who is alienating us?"
I told him right away...
that it was Ji Min.
Ji Min, are you getting
the elimination immunity pass today?
Me? We haven't talked about that yet.
Really? Why don't you go with us?
- To the Deathmatch.
- I'm fine with that.
- I like that idea.
- I'm all right with that.
We don't care who goes.
Then, you'll be at a disadvantage.
We'll beat you to death.
I can beat you by myself too.
So, you're going to the Deathmatch
with us.
- Yes, that sounds fun.
- Okay?
He got under my skin,
and I was offended.
So, I was determined to defeat them.
How much are you spending
on the black hole?
We can't move the black hole.
I recommend getting the star.
I bet Ji Hoo and Seung Yong will
also come for the star.
Hye Seon, YunB, and I can't get
to the star, anyway.
With the rest of the members,
it's about who's placing first,
so that doesn't matter.
Hye Seon, YunB, and I need to go
where it's safe.
So, the three of us will go
to Sector Eight...
and stay safe.
One of us...
The one who has the most coins
can get the black hole...
(Dwarf planet, cosmic dust)
The three of us can't risk going down...
because they might move it again.
To prevent that,
we have to spend about 17 coins
to move it here.
That rules out the possibilities
of our loss.
I believe they moved the black hole
to the star.
Unfortunately,
I happened to be...
at the star's sector.
That's when we decided...
to control the black hole
as much as we can.
We had seven members,
so we could utilize most of the coins.
How may I help you?
I'll buy some coins.
Ji Min, 10,000 dollars will be deducted
from your funds.
Okay.
I'll bet 18 coins on the black hole...
and send it to Sector 13.
(Black hole, 18 coins, Sector 13)
(She spent all her coins.)
I've received 18 coins.
(Points earned in Round 7)
Round Seven has ended.
Round Eight will now begin...
and run for 30 minutes.
(Points earned, total score)
The star's energy is now four,
and it's turned into a supernova.
The players in the supernova's sector...
will lose five points
starting in this round.
Now,
to blow up the black hole,
we need 12 more coins.
We spend 13 coins or more
one more time, and it's game over.
Are you worried that they'll send it
to the supernova sector?
One variable was...
that they could move to the supernova...
while sending the black hole...
to themselves.
Then, the supernova's negativity
becomes positivity,
so they all earn five points.
These new strategies could come up,
so we tried to stop their extra plans...
in the remaining rounds.
Here are the results of the last round.
(Points earned in Round 8)
(Points earned, total score)
Beom didn't even enter, right?
I don't think so.
I don't think Beom entered.
That's the only way we get those results.
He's decided to go to the Deathmatch.
He's trying to pick between the two.
The game is already over.
I don't know what they're calculating now.
Me neither.
Why are they still gathering
to have a discussion?
Are they coming up with a new comedy skit?
I talked to Beom,
and they already agreed...
that Seung Yong and Beom...
would go to the Deathmatch.
The round ends in one minute.
- Already.
- It's going to be a problem.
That's why they're resting.
- They're resting already.
- They gave up.
Yes, those two already made up
their minds...
to go to the Deathmatch.
That way, they can save Ji Hoo.
I mean, Ji Hoo didn't do anything wrong.
You either leave tomorrow or today.
There's no one's fault here.
- Exactly.
- That's the game we're playing,
so we're only trying to justify ourselves.
- We at least need the justification.
- Exactly.
This way, we get revenge for yesterday.
- We're finishing...
- Right.
a story.
They're hopeless now.
It's almost over.
It's finally over.
Finally.
I hope it's a memorization game.
Memorization?
I have a good memory.
Really? I'll count on you.
You do that.
Thinking about going to the Deathmatch,
I started accepting my fate.
I felt more lethargic.
I was just hoping it would end soon.
It was so exhausting.
I just lay there with them.
Team R wasn't there...
when we joined forces
and attacked Team P1.
Right.
They had so much fun...
when they gathered all the others
to attack Team P2 and us.
They're dispirited since it's their
first time being on the receiving end.
That happens the first time. Also,
it's their first time
on a survival show...
and getting ganged up on.
Naturally, their attitude goes,
"Why are we playing this..."
- "in the first place?"
- Right.
I understand them.
It's not exactly an appropriate reaction.
You ought to do your best
even when you're losing.
When you're on a survival show,
you're put in such unfair situations.
And Bloody Game tells you
from the get-go...
that it's an irrational and unfair game.
If we hadn't started it,
they would have done it to us.
And this happens frequently...
on survival shows.
YunB is so cute. He went to them...
and tried to sway them by talking
about justifications and narratives.
- While he did that,
- He hinted to them about Ji Min.
he ruled out the possibility...
of being chosen.
People are so funny.
In the end, they formed a team to win.
But he flattered the opponents...
- so that they wouldn't pick him.
- Now that it's nearing the end,
he went and made sure
that he wouldn't be picked.
You have every right to do that.
- But I can clearly see how he's doing.
- Right.
It's cute, though.
There are many survival methods.
Round Nine has ended.
Round 10 will now begin
and run for 30 minutes.
It's over.
The leader has been decided.
Where do you want to go?
I'll go where I want to go this time.
- Okay.
- We can all go wherever we want.
It's the last round, after all.
(Majority Alliance's victory
has been decided.)
I'll go and transfer.
The funds? You both have to go in.
- What?
- You both have to go in for that.
We're giving all the remaining energy...
to Ji Hoo.
We decided to hand him over...
our entire strength and perish...
like the stars.
Kwak Beom would like to transfer...
his entire funds...
to Kang Ji Hoo.
Kwak Beom's personal funds
of 20,000 dollars...
will be transferred to Kang Ji Hoo.
I'd like to transfer my funds.
(Seung Yong gives Ji Hoo 20,000 dollars.)
Round Ten has ended.
The final results will be announced soon.
Who should we pick?
But I heard
that Sung Joo had already earned...
an elimination immunity pass.
- Really?
- He was promised.
Hye Seon and YunB said so.
They said that was the team's opinion.
But it might not be true. Keun Woo...
will suggest giving it to Ji Min.
Then, what's our list?
I'm still torn.
I honestly want to play with Ji Min.
So do I.
She was the primary reason
that led to all of this.
She had formed a majority alliance,
so it'll teach her...
a good lesson for her life
to be attacked by one.
An eye for an eye,
and a tooth for a tooth, right?
That's true.
She caused our loss,
so it's only fair
that she also risks something.
She should have risked
one of her fingers, at least.
I don't know how it will go.
I need to take Ji Min to the Deathmatch.
But what we're worried about is...
We had talked about it until Round Ten.
If Ji Min places first, we can't pick her.
Or she made a deal with someone...
to receive the immunity pass.
Then, our plan won't work.
What are you...
staring at, Beom?
It just looks like it's been decided.
Yes.
- You didn't go in?
- There are six points apart...
Why aren't you going to the Voting Room?
My work is done.
I've already given him everything.
I gave him my entire funds.
This is all meaningless.
Even if I make a move,
it's only one sector at a time.
We also haven't chosen number one.
It's going to be random.
Who are you going to pick
for the Deathmatch?
I'm not sure yet.
Could you share it with us...
if you decide who to pick?
We also...
have no idea.
We want to know who you'd pick and why.
But when it's announced...
You're right.
- We'll have to share anyway.
- You're right.
For now... I don't know.
This is Bloody Game.
A game with no fair play.
I'll pay them back in kind.
This is the situation we're in.
We're deciding who to put in first place.
As a matter of fact,
it's either Seong Beom...
or Ji Min.
Darn it, seriously.
Why is he the one planning all this?
That punk.
I don't get it.
YunB doesn't want to go to Deathmatch.
Right.
- Okay.
- He can't say that. Darn it.
That's why he is racking his brain
right now.
He's spewing nonsense.
He doesn't want to go?
Who here wants to go to Deathmatch?
I told you. Why talk about that
in the middle of the game?
He'd check others here and there
to build a justification.
You've got to be kidding me. Darn.
That doesn't make sense.
Why doesn't he step forward, then?
And he doesn't want to go.
I felt upset because...
YunB was talking about...
who the perpetrators and victims were.
And I was like,
"Who are you to talk about that?"
He doesn't have the right to say that.
Still,
you went through a lot,
overcoming an unexpected obstacle.
- Seriously.
- Yes.
- Right.
- Well done.
- We did well.
Honestly, I think that team lost...
because they gave up in the middle.
- They had a high chance of winning too.
- Right.
They could've changed their supernova.
Yes, there was a rule...
- about supernova turning the tables.
- Right.
They had a way to win,
- but they didn't. That's why they lost.
- You're rubbing salt in their wound.
That's what I honestly think.
You never know until the end,
but they lost.
That's why they got
the zero percent chance of winning.
- That's right.
- So,
what I'm saying is,
we don't have to try and understand them.
We just need to stick to our plan.
He's right. Based on the structure
of Bloody Game,
if you planned the game,
you should take responsibility to the end.
Ji Hoo, what's your thought?
I agree.
The Money Challenge results
will now be announced.
The bottom player
of the Money Challenge is...
(Kwak Beom)
Kwak Beom.
So cool.
Your name was announced
for the first time.
(Shin Seung Yong)
It's Shin Seung Yong.
Gosh.
- It's a fight between two titans.
- Next,
today's Money Challenge winner
will now be announced.
The winner of today's Money Challenge...
It was important to see
who won first place.
The most important thing was to avoid
Ji Min from getting first place.
That's what I prayed for.
That's what I kept praying for.
"Please don't come in first."
It's Heo Seong Beom.
(The winner of Money Challenge,
Heo Seong Beom)
You go to the comet,
and Sung Joo, come to the satellite.
That's because even if Sung Joo
wins 5 points, he can't win 1st place.
- It's impossible.
- Okay.
Sung Joo, come to the satellite.
The strategy was to make...
the one who won first place...
to join first place.
Seong Beom and I had similar scores.
But Seong Beom had coins
he could use to move,
so that's why I think
Seong Beom went first.
I'll move to Sector Two.
I'll move my sector.
You need three coins.
- Will you use them?
- Yes.
(He earned 5 points in Round 9.)
You have submitted three coins.
You've been relocated to Sector One.
(Won 1st place in Round 10
with 31 points in total)
(Project Galaxy Final Results)
(Seong Beom: 31, Ji Min: 30,
Keun Woo: 22, Sung Joo: 19, YunB: 17,)
(Hye Seon: 14, Jin Ho: 14, Ji Hoo: minus
2, Seung Yong: minus 3, Beom: minus 30)
The winner, Heo Seong Beom,
enter the Voting Room right now...
and receive 20,000 dollars,
your personal funds.
Also, choose a player you can transfer
the elimination immunity pass to.
It made me think a lot.
At first, I thought of Sung Joo naturally,
and that's because he joined us
after abandoning his team.
And regarding that, his former team
could target him.
And Ji Min.
Ji Min's been too much focused
by the opponents as a target,
so I kept wondering who I should
give the elimination immunity pass to...
until the end.
(Grunting)
This is 20,000 dollars, the winning prize
of the Money Challenge.
We'll store the funds you received
in the safe.
Thank you.
Except for Beom and Seung Yong,
who are at the bottom,
choose a player who will be exempt
from the elimination, just like you.
My choice...
(He's done choosing the player who's
exempted by using the immunity pass.)
(Sighing)
Those who are excluded
from getting eliminated...
through being given
the elimination immunity pass...
from the winner of today's
Money Challenge, Heo Seong Beom is...
"Please don't get
the elimination immunity pass."
Now,
we've got to kill Ji Min.
It's Hong Jin Ho.
That's only right.
Well done.
For one,
I voted for Jin Ho
who showed great performance today.
I respect Sung Joo's decision,
and so do I respect Ji Min's.
But I concluded it'd be iffy
to side with either one.
If I gave it to one of them,
the other side can choose Jin Ho
for the Deathmatch.
I worried about that.
The biggest reason...
was him playing the biggest role
in today's game.
The bottom players
of today's Money Challenge,
Beom and Seung Yong,
please enter the Voting Room 1 by 1.
Then pick a person whom you'd like...
to join the Deathmatch.
Jin Ho got the elimination immunity pass,
and I thought, "Nice!"
"It's a vast expanse."
Nothing is involved with them.
Let's go.
But who was I to choose?
We wanted to drag Ji Min to Deathmatch,
but if we were to bring
an irrelevant person,
they'd join it.
Then, what should we do?
I was going to pick Jin Ho.
Darn.
What shall we do?
Honestly, I find Sung Joo annoying,
but I think it'll be better...
- if he advances.
- Yes, I think that'll be better too.
Let's go with Keun Woo and Ji Min.
- K and J?
- Yes.
Let's stick with ruining a team.
Otherwise, it'd get iffy.
If we choose both of them,
the votes will be split...
and we'll get the objective votes.
But if we go for Keun Woo and Ji Min,
Keun Woo would step forward.
- I'm certain.
- Keun Woo?
Yes. Wouldn't you think so too?
Can I hear
what you guys are talking about?
- Of course.
- Yes. Come here.
(Ji Hoo in the same alliance joins them.)
Ji Hoo, we were talking
about Keun Woo and Ji Min.
He expected
that Keun Woo would go ahead...
- and say they should choose him.
- For sure.
That's for sure.
But based on the others' minds...
There's a chance they won't pick Keun Woo.
That's right.
There's more than enough chance
for them to choose Ji Min.
I think...
I mean, we could pick Hye Seon and Ji Min,
for example.
Then P3 team will definitely vote
for Hye Seon.
Seeing the odds, Hye Seon barely has
a chance to be chosen.
- Well done. Good luck. But...
- Okay.
- What?
- If...
I want to strike a deal.
Well,
if you choose YunB...
Regardless of what has happened so far...
Even if we have to pay for you guys...
Ji Min and I can guide the right path
for you.
How much are you willing to give?
How much do you want from Ji Min and me?
- Me?
- I think 60,000 dollars will do.
- You want 60,000 dollars?
- Yes.
Then we can give you 20,000 dollars each
and make that 40,000 dollars.
For the first time,
I struck a deal with Beom and Seung Yong.
If they were to choose YunB,
Ji Min and I would give them
20,000 dollars each.
You're saying if I chose YunB,
you'd give me your money.
That can't be helped.
I'm sorry I couldn't choose you.
Not at all.
- You two carried the game,
- No.
so this is only right.
If it had been to be yielded between two,
I'd have picked one specifically.
- This is only right. Come here.
- But you both were...
Let's get some air.
Based on what I talked with Keun Woo,
I think it'd be best for us
if YunB leaves.
I'm not certain about that.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Shouldn't they pick YunB first?
I told Keun Woo to make a deal with them
about that.
I see.
If we were to make something fun...
(20 minutes ago)
It's to make them choose YunB.
Then we'll only need to vote
and make YunB gone.
You're right.
Do you think we could make a deal
with them?
To whom?
You're close to Beom,
so make a deal with Beom.
Tell them we'll abandon YunB.
If they choose him,
and if Seung Yong wins at the Deathmatch,
then we won't exclude him
from the next round...
and play with him as his team.
Tell them about that.
Okay, I'll talk to them.
If it doesn't work,
you could mention the funds.
- Okay.
- I have enough money too.
Let's get on with that.
(Based on what Ji Min asked,)
(Keun Woo made a deal.)
I was really bothered
by YunB playing politics at the end,
and it got on my nerves so much.
It ruined my mood completely.
So I thought it'd be better
to get rid of YunB...
who is stirring things up.
Choose a player
you'd like to play Deathmatch with.
You've chosen Park Ji Min.
I'm sorry.
Seung Yong,
please leave this area right now...
and prepare for the Deathmatch.
Okay.
Choose a player you'd like to
play Deathmatch with.
Beom, please leave this area right now
and prepare for the Deathmatch.
You're not allowed to talk
with other players.
Okay.
Here are the results.
The player chosen for Deathmatch is...
(Park Ji Min)
It's Park Ji Min.
I kind of expected it.
I thought they thought of me
as the leader.
If that's why they picked me,
then it's a bit...
of an ugly choice.
The second player chosen
for Deathmatch is...
(Jeong Keun Woo)
It's Jeong Keun Woo.
It happened to be...
Keun Woo, none other than others.
You've chosen Jeong Keun Woo.
(Beom chose Keun Woo.)
I think...
if I had to choose two people from P1,
then...
people wouldn't vote for Keun Woo.
Two members of Team P1 were chosen,
so I wasn't too glad.
Jeong Keun Woo and Park Ji Min.
You'll vote between the two candidates.
Players, please vote for one player...
to proceed to Deathmatch.
The vote will end in an hour.
(The vote begins.)
Well, this is...
My gosh.
- This is...
- It's funny.
Ji Min, I met you face-to-face.
Come here.
Don't see this.
Those old men would play politics.
They'd make crazy deals,
and Keun Woo and Ji Min would intervene.
Team P3 would calculate their moves.
Hye Seon would say,
pretending she's close to them.
I just didn't want any of that.
(He enters the Voting Room right away.)
(Park Ji Min, Jeong Keun Woo)
(Kang Ji Hoo votes for Park Ji Min.)
Just as Beom and Seung Yong wanted,
I wanted Ji Min...
and Seung Yong to have a face off.
I came out after voting for Ji Min.
(Sighing)
I mean, I didn't get to say goodbye.
But they just went in.
They must've not known
they'd be dragged right away.
I was so lonely and desolate.
I was so upset.
Gosh, this is hard.
I'm all alone now,
so there's no one talking to me,
and those who do...
don't really care for me...
nor do they show their affection.
I feel like I've actually lost
all my family.
Ji Hoo was on the other side,
so he'd follow their order.
Ji Min and Keun Woo, if you have anything
to say, say it now.
And please leave,
- so we can talk by ourselves.
- Okay.
If you stay,
they won't be able to say anything.
Shall we do that?
First, I...
I was there yesterday,
and today...
I might have to go.
That'll depend on you guys, though.
I have a winning strategy.
I'll come back.
- I'll be able to come back.
- I'll come back.
I got rid of Xitsuh and Tae Gyun.
Exactly. I feel like
he'll come back for sure.
I'll come back.
- I can also come back.
- I'm a gold medalist, you see.
- That hurts my pride.
- I'm the devil at second base.
Don't touch me.
You should give it a shot
and make it cool.
I'll throw Seung Yong away.
What?
- Hey, what is this?
- Come on.
She must have no credit...
that no one's responding.
- What...
- I can't do this because it's so cringe.
Don't make me do this.
I can't do things like this.
- Try it again.
- I can't.
Before time goes,
decide it quickly and tell us.
- Hang out by yourselves.
- Okay.
- Let's go to our room.
(Keun Woo and Ji Min exit.)
I feel so bad.
- I'm telling you.
- Do we look easy?
I think this is why...
they picked us.
Someone they think they can beat...
and the mastermind.
I think that's why they picked us.
Gosh, what do we do?
If it's two-thirds, the chance is high,
despite luck and skills.
It's one-thirds. Only one survives.
I know. Two-thirds of them go home.
Beom is smart too.
Everyone here is good at games.
He just says funny things, but he's smart.
No one is bad at games.
We don't know who will win
at the Deathmatch.
It's not surprising...
- if any of them survives.
- Right.
Then who should survive for us to benefit?
I don't want Ji Min to go, then.
The risk is too high. It's two-thirds.
Because today, Ji Min...
sacrificed herself.
- I know...
- That's true.
she threw a bomb in the middle,
but she used her coins...
- She bought five coins too.
- True.
She thought it'd be better
to have more people on her side,
so she took Sung Joo.
- That...
- She's a strategist.
It wasn't completely convincing,
but I think she'd have tried hard...
even if she failed.
So, I think she contributed more...
compared to Keun Woo.
That's for sure.
I gave it a thought.
If they have
a 1-in-3 chance of coming back,
the chance is slim.
I just didn't like the fact
that Ji Min was in that kind of danger.
I don't want to take any risk
of her going.
Her going to Deathmatch.
But we should vote with the thought
of one of them going home.
I know. That's why...
I've decided.
Me? Honestly speaking,
I'm leaning toward Ji Min.
I know it sounds brutal,
but even if she loses,
she has the chance to kill Seung Yong.
You want Ji Min to go and fight them?
Let her wield the knife herself.
I think that's...
- It's...
- I don't know.
We gather with a consensus...
and a great cause.
But when it comes to Deathmatch,
you let her hold the knife
and fight to survive.
It's too harsh on her.
It is.
But there's a chance of her winning too.
I'll go and vote.
Sorry, Keun Woo.
(Choi Hye Seon votes for Jeong Keun Woo.)
What are you going to do?
Me? I'm doing the math in my head.
Based on what I worked out,
Ji Min has a higher chance.
- Of letting her go?
- Yes.
Actually...
We should vote on our own.
Based on how they played today,
- then we should save Ji Min.
- Yes.
But today wasn't the only day.
There was yesterday and the day before.
- The first day too.
- There's tomorrow too.
Given that situation...
Actually, yesterday...
Keun Woo...
- went...
- Because he went instead of others?
He took one for the team.
Keun Woo is like this.
When that situation comes,
Keun Woo is the one who goes,
"Send me away."
He always took the bullet.
Right. It's the same situation
for two days straight.
I'm not sure if it's right
to send him away for two days straight...
just to save ourselves.
I understand Keun Woo's position.
I understand his heart...
and I make that decision
from time to time.
This is what it is.
I'm sure he wants to survive as well,
but there are younger ones
doing their best.
When a Deathmatch situation occurs,
he goes, "Just pick me."
Whenever these situations came,
it felt like there was a tendency
of sending him away like a scapegoat.
That made me feel very uncomfortable.
It's a form of sacrifice.
One sacrifice can be made
by the older guy,
but I believe this can't be repeated.
(Park Ji Min, Jeong Keun Woo)
(Hong Jin Ho votes for Park Ji Min.)
This is my vote.
As his friend...
and someone who occasionally
makes those decisions,
I didn't think it was right for the
same thing to happen two days straight.
That was the reason behind
voting for Ji Min.
I'm sorry.
(I'm sorry.)
(YunB votes for Park Ji Min.)
I'm voting for the one
who will be in the Deathmatch, right?
That's right.
(Heo Seong Beom completes his vote.)
(Hyun Sung Joo completes his vote.)
(Choi Hye Seon voted for Jeong Keun Woo.)
(Kang Ji Hoo, Hong Jin Ho, and Yun B
voted for Park Ji Min.)
(Heo Seong Beom and Hyun Sung Joo's
votes are unrevealed.)
I got so attached to them.
They were the ones I've always liked.
I really enjoyed being their teammates.
Even so, I had to survive.
I came this far. Winning in this survival
is about to be achieved.
It's upsetting, but it can't be helped.
(The last one to vote, Jeong Keun Woo)
(Park Ji Min, Jeong Keun Woo)
Whenever these situations come,
I always say I'll be the one to go.
I believe that's what a team leader...
and adults must do.
Ji Min has gone through
many different trials...
and experienced many survival shows,
but I want to be the one
to deal with those situations.
I told this to Jin Ho several times
and he scolded me.
Earlier, I mentioned...
- that I wanted to be in the Deathmatch.
- You offered to go.
Whenever things like Deathmatches pop up,
you don't have to offer yourself up.
- Okay.
- Right.
It's okay to make that move once.
- It's bad to do that constantly.
- Okay. I'll stop now.
- Right. You should stop.
- Right.
You're right.
I totally understand him.
He's a guy who does his best.
He's a guy who has great leadership
for the team.
I understand it when a guy like that
says that to me.
But...
I have a heart that wants
to protect my team at all costs.
(Park Ji Min, Jeong Keun Woo)
(Jeong Keun Woo votes for Jeong Keun Woo.)
You don't know anything, right?
Nobody revealed anything.
I don't even know what Ji Hoo is thinking.
It makes sense for Ji Hoo
to do this or that.
But whoever goes,
- I think they'll make it back.
- Or in Ji Hoo's situation,
he managed to survive.
The worst thing for him is
to be the only one left in his team.
He's incredible.
He kept surviving thanks to the sacrifice
of his teammates,
but he's tearless.
(Ji Hoo was lying alone in the room.)
I went to my room...
and lay down on Kyoung Hoon's bed.
I tried my best not to cry,
but...
I shed so many tears.
I cried my eyes out.
I caught a cold while doing the missions
of Bloody Game.
I thought I had to take some pills.
I thought that I had to eat something
in 50 minutes.
I found the rice cup
the older guys brought.
I was going to eat the rice cup, but...
How is this made?
The older guys used to make this for me.
After getting reminded of that,
I cried my eyes out
while reading the directions.
I had to eat before the voting time ended.
I ate while crying.
It was a Top Three moment...
of me crying in my life.
I cried even harder...
than when I broke up with my girlfriend.
The vote has ended.
Please gather in the main hall.
Gosh, it felt like yesterday
when it was loud in here.
- The group has become this small already?
- There are not many of us left.
The vote result will now be announced.
The player to enter the Deathmatch...
(Park Ji Min)
is Park Ji Min.
This is a better result. I'll be back.
I'm voting for the one
who will be in the Deathmatch, right?
That's right.
(Heo Seong Beom votes for Park Ji Min.)
Please return with a win.
This was the reason I went with.
We played the Killer Game yesterday.
The reason I was able to narrow down
Ji Min and Tae Gyun the fastest...
was because of Ji Min's mistake.
But later on,
Ji Min didn't even enter the Deathmatch.
Xitsuh ended up going home as a result.
Instead of sending Keun Woo for no reason,
I thought that it would be better
for Ji Min to go and return after a win...
to strengthen our team's next play.
(Park Ji Min, Jeong Keun Woo)
I will return with a win.
(Park Ji Min votes for Park Ji Min.)
I picked up the sword.
I picked up the sword with my own hand.
(Jeong Keun Woo: Choi Hye Seon,
Hyun Sung Joo, Jeong Keun Woo)
(Park Ji Min: Kang Ji Hoo, Hong Jin Ho,
YunB, Heo Seong Beom, Park Ji Min)
Park Ji Min,
please leave this area right now...
- and prepare for the Deathmatch.
- I'll place first.
- Beat all of them!
- You must place first!
- Thank you!
- You must beat all of them!
Come back with a win.
You're saying
I'm better than Jeong Keun Woo.
- Right.
- Come back with a win!
Come back with a win.
Deathmatch players,
please gather in the main hall.
I hope it's something like guessing
the names of soccer team emblems.
Guessing the engine displacement of cars.
Hello.
(Park Ji Min, the one these two wished
to see, has come.)
We'll be going against each other again.
Good game.
Good game, have fun.
We were waiting for her.
I thought that Ji Min was the one
who came up with this structure.
I really wanted to crush her.
Ji Min joins the Deathmatch.
No matter what game,
I was determined to beat her.
Even if it was about mathematics
which I'm terrible at,
I was determined to do my best
to beat her.
I was picked for being a key figure?
They just came up with that reason...
to be able to send me away.
It was such an unimpressive reason.
I'm no key figure.
It's because you are already
a public enemy.
You will become a public enemy
even the next day.
Before others get blood on their hands,
I'll slit your throat first.
Kwak Beom.
Shin Seung Yong.
Park Ji Min.
These three players
have entered the Deathmatch.
Only one winner will survive...
and the other players will get eliminated.
Today's Deathmatch will be revealed.
Today's Deathmatch...
is Mix and Match.
Mix and Match...
is a game in which you must find
the right word...
after putting together the locations
of the black spaces...
of the grids
that get revealed successively.
A total of 12 rounds will be played.
In each round,
grids with the empty spaces
and black spaces...
will be revealed in order
after three seconds.
Players must align the grids
to form the word...
and find the answer.
The words are all from
the Standard Korean Language Dictionary.
When a player calls out to say the answer,
the answer must be called out
within five seconds.
When it's the right answer,
two-character words are worth two points.
Three-character words are
worth three points.
Four-character words are
worth four points.
When it's an incorrect answer,
one point will get deducted...
and the player must wait 30 seconds
to call out the answer again.
After 12 rounds,
the player with the highest score
will survive.
When the scores are the same,
the player who has answered
more questions will survive.
Mix and Match will begin shortly.
I'm not that quick. This is bad.
It's the same name as the game played
in Season Three's final.
When I thought about the games played
in Season Three,
I didn't feel confident.
But I might find a way out...
if I stay focused.
This can be a game...
that I can be good at.
- Right.
That's what scares me.
This game?
It's a game of addition.
Adding up the pictures.
I started drawing at a young age...
and I entered an art school.
The first thing I mentioned about myself
was my spatial ability.
I have a talent in that area...
and I believe I have an advantage.
I hope they're simple words instead.
I felt really confident.
"The words are all from
the Standard Korean Language Dictionary."
That line struck me.
"I'm an announcer."
"A game like this had to come out
for the Deathmatch."
"Finding the word?"
It seemed like I had a good chance
for this game.
We will begin Round One.
The two-character word will be revealed.
(Round 1, 2-character word)
It seemed like Braille.
"Should I squint..."
"and leave afterimages?"
As the interval was a lot longer
than I thought,
I couldn't see any afterimages.
I had to start over each time.
Here's my answer!
Shin Seung Yong.
It's "dalgyal."
- That is correct.
- You are correct.
You get two points.
Here's the answer.
(Dalgyal)
"Gyal" was like that?
I figured out "dal."
"Gyal" threw me off.
The letters are written on a grid.
The way it's written is really important.
The first thing I did was to...
figure out the final consonants.
I figured out if the word
had final consonants or not.
If the word had final consonants,
I looked for the vowels.
Then, I looked for the first consonants.
This was the order of my deduction.
I'm quick with linguistics.
We will begin Round Two.
(Round 2 begins.)
The two-character word will be revealed.
(Round 2, 2-character word)
The length of the first consonants,
the length of the vowels,
and the length of the final consonants.
I couldn't...
figure them out at all.
I felt totally lost.
Whether it was mieum, ieung,
kiyuk, or nieun,
I could slowly tell what they were.
Here's my answer!
Kwak Beom.
(Kwak Beom makes his attempt
to answer the question.)
"Ilgeup."
- That is incorrect.
- Gosh.
You get one point deducted.
You can call out for the answer
after 30 seconds.
What is this?
I thought that it wasn't "ilgeup"
right away.
I thought that the second final consonant
was nieun.
Here's my answer.
Shin Seung Yong.
"Myulgyun."
- That is correct.
- What?
You get two points.
(Myulgyun)
Gosh.
That's what it looks like.
"I should look at this differently."
I got the hang of it at the start.
Gosh, I'm at minus one.
I can do this.
We will begin Round Three.
(Round 3, 2-character word)
I was certain that...
the second character was "tong."
I wasn't sure about the first character.
I found rieul.
I also figured out
that the second character was "tong."
Here's my answer!
Kwak Beom.
"Piltong."
- That is incorrect.
- Gosh!
You get one point deducted.
Here's my answer.
Shin Seung Yong.
"Kkoltong."
- That is incorrect.
- Here's my answer!
Park Ji Min.
(Park Ji Min makes her attempt
to answer the question.)
"Kkultong."
That is correct.
You get two points.
Why did he get it wrong for "kkoltong?"
- It's "kkultong," not "kkoltong."
- "Kkultong."
- It's "kkultong?"
- Yes.
"Kkoltong?"
I hesitated to call that one out
as the answer.
There are many words
that turn out to be standard words.
But even if it was a standard word,
I assumed that...
the word couldn't be used for a show.
Seung Yong happened
to call that one out...
and I was able to use that
to my advantage.
It's "kkultong?"
It felt like I put the answer
on a plate for Ji Min.
It was quite upsetting.
(Kkultong)
We will begin Round Four.
(Round 4, 2-character word)
I started to get the hang of it
from Round Four.
But...
Here's my answer!
Kwak Beom.
"Napddaem."
That is correct.
You get two points.
- "Napdam?"
- "Napddaem."
"Napddaem!"
A strategy slowly started to form.
The consonants and vowels.
A, ya, eo, yeo.
I figured those out first.
I was able to spot
the final consonants after that.
Ssang digeut.
"Napddaem."
(Napddaem)
I can see them now.
Beom got the answer really quickly
and I got surprised.
Beom figured out "napddaem"
really quickly.
My heart started to beat really fast...
because he kept picking up the pace.
We will begin Round Five.
(Round 5 begins.)
(Round 5, 2-character word)
Here's my answer.
Kwak Beom.
That's not it.
"Kwonryeok."
(Kwonreok)
That is correct.
- That was so hard.
- You get two points.
- Gosh.
- The first character was really tough.
Here's the answer.
(Kwonryeok)
I figured out
how the letters were written on the grid.
I can figure out
the second character somehow,
but the first character is really tough.
It was hard to figure out the words
with two vowels.
"When there are two vowels,"
"this is how they're written on the grid."
That was how I got the hang of it.
- What do I do with three characters?
- Gosh.
We will begin Round Six.
The three-character word will be revealed.
What do I do with three characters?
(3 characters, 4 grid sheets)
Oh, gosh.
(Round 6, 3-character word)
There were three characters.
I couldn't even figure out
where each character ended.
There was an extra character
I had to figure out on top of that.
It felt like a reset.
I was confused about
whether a certain part...
was included in the same character.
I did this with my hand
because I couldn't tell.
I wanted to focus on just one character.
As I wasn't sure about the spacing
between the characters,
I thought it became much harder.
I started with the spacing
between the characters...
and I looked for the final consonants
of each character.
Here's my answer.
Shin Seung Yong.
(Shin Seung Yong makes his attempt
to answer the question.)
"Dongmulkwon."
That is incorrect.
What did you say?
You get one point deducted.
"Donggulkwon?"
No.
Here's my answer!
Kwak Beom.
"Dongmulwon."
That is correct.
- Gosh!
- No!
You get three points.
- It was "dongmulwon."
- Here's the answer.
(Dongmulwon)
I thought that I did
all that hard work again for nothing.
Points get deducted for incorrect answers,
so I thought that...
I had to answer the questions
as carefully and quickly as possible.
We will begin Round Seven.
The three-character word will be revealed.
(Round 7, 3-character word)
After considering the characters
with two vowels in mind,
I noticed that the last character
had two vowels.
Here's my answer.
Shin Seung Yong.
(Shin Seung Yong makes his attempt
to answer the question.)
"Sangpoomgwon."
That is correct.
As the rounds went by so quickly,
I found it really tough.
While solving the questions,
I found some ways...
to make my deductions faster.
I played the game with just the thought...
of wanting to be faster than the others.
(Sangpoomgwon)
We will begin Round Eight.
(Round 8, 3-character word)
(Beom and Seung Yong are tied right now.)
I figured out that the character in
the middle didn't have a final consonant.
Here's my answer.
Shin Seung Yong.
"Tongjorim."
That is correct.
You get three points.
I only found "tongjo."
Here's the answer.
(Tongjorim)
I almost got there.
We will begin Round Nine.
(Round 9, 3-character word)
What is that?
I have to throw a pickoff.
If I don't get it right,
the others might take the points.
I have to take my chance.
Here's my answer!
Kwak Beom.
(Kwak Beom makes his attempt
to answer the question.)
"Jeongwangpan."
That is correct.
- You get three points.
- The one in the middle was really tough.
- How are we supposed to find "gwang?"
- Here's the answer.
(Jeongwangpan)
It was a game that I adapted to more
after each round.
How are things now? We're tied.
"Okay. Let's focus even more."
Getting the four-character words right...
was more beneficial,
so I told myself not to be complacent.
We will begin Round Ten.
The four-character word will be revealed.
(Round 10, 4-character word)
This is what it looks like?
Are there more tiles?
Gosh, this is insane.
I struggled so much with 3 characters.
I had to deal with 4 now.
I was about to go crazy.
I still urged myself
to fight until the end.
I counted the tiles on the grid.
I wanted to divide them into quarters.
But I wasn't sure if there were 40 tiles.
It was so far away.
It also seemed like there were 50 tiles.
I spent all my time doing that.
Here's my answer!
"Boolhyeophwaeum."
Park Ji Min.
That is correct.
You get four points.
There were four characters,
but I got the answer
much faster than I expected.
"I think I got the hang of it now."
"If I pick up the pace a bit,"
"I'll have a chance."
(Boolhyeophwaeum)
Four-pointers are crucial...
and I might lose the lead.
I tried to focus until the end.
Ji Min is an announcer.
She'll know ten times more
of the words I have in my brain.
I'm under the gun now.
We will begin Round 11.
(There are two questions left.)
(Round 11, 4-character word)
If I get stuck on the first character,
I must quickly move on
to the second character.
If I get stuck on the 2nd character,
I must move on to the 3rd character...
and try to get
at least one character right...
to be able to find the word.
When there are four characters,
four-character idioms come to mind.
With four-character idioms,
I thought that I could make a guess...
even with one character.
I figured out most of the characters.
But I suddenly got confused
and wondered if...
the final consonant was nieun or mieum.
Here's my answer.
Shin Seung Yong.
"Cheongcheonbyeokryeok."
- That's the right answer.
- Gosh!
That is correct.
Gosh, that's right.
- You get four points.
- Gosh!
(Cheongcheonbyeokryeok)
I must get all of them right
to catch up with him.
(Kwak Beom must win Round 12
for an extra round.)
We will begin Round 12.
The four-character word will be revealed.
(Round 12, 4-character word)
I found up to "dongbang."
"Dongbangjigook?"
The answer was found.
It was a battle of quick reflexes because
I found out most of the characters.
Gosh, I must go for it.
- Here's my answer!
Who was faster?
(Shin Seung Yong was faster.)
I had to make the call right away.
I was a fool for not being able to.
Shin Seung Yong.
"Dongbyeongsangryeon."
(Dongbyeongsangryeon)
That is correct.
It's over.
You get four points.
(Dongbyeongsangryeon)
- Was that it?
- Yes.
(Kwak Beom: 8, Shin Seung Yong: 16,
Park Ji Min: 6)
You've gone through so much...
- Great work, Seung Yong.
- to stay up this late.
You've gone through a lot as well.
You've gone through so much.
It was very disappointing
that I wasn't able...
to go to the semi-finals with Beom,
but I was able to achieve my main goal.
Well done.
It was quite disappointing.
This game was based on pure skill.
The two of us still did well
to do the revenge.
It would've been great to purge...
the one I had as a target.
It's quite disappointing
that I wasn't able to achieve that.
But as I did my best,
I have no regrets.
Seung Yong did well to win the game.
Although it's disappointing,
I perfectly acknowledge my defeat.
The Deathmatch has ended.
Everyone, please gather in the main hall.
The Deathmatch results
will now be announced.
The players eliminated
from Bloody Game X are...
Kwak Beom...
(Kwak Beom)
(Park Ji Min)
and Park Ji Min.
Kwak Beom and Park Ji Min,
please pack your bags immediately...
and leave the Bloody Mansion.
Eliminated players can never return
to Bloody Game X.
I failed to wing it.
It didn't work out.
Make the purge happen tomorrow.
We weren't able to be on the same team
until the end.
- Not even once.
- Exactly.
- Fit me in next time.
- Right.
- Of course.
I felt relieved with everything...
after experiencing the Deathmatch.
I believe Bloody Game...
has all types of human figures.
There are those who are incredibly clever.
I couldn't find a single one.
But there are people like me as well.
I wanted to show people
that I could survive...
even with a lack of brainpower.
The moment I want to relive?
It has to be the Mafia Game.
"The arrest of the killer
has been successful."
I want to relive that moment.
The dopamine I felt during that moment.
"Why do the same people
keep appearing on survival shows?"
"Why is that person on every single time?"
It's an addiction.
A dopamine addiction.
Let's say...
it's a sport.
One can play soccer
until they run out of breath...
or ride a bike at dangerous speeds...
to feel this sense of thrill.
But here,
that thrill can be felt
while sitting in my seat.
It was the greatest level of dopamine
I could've experienced.
I feel thankful to be able to participate
in such an exciting game.
I had fun.
I wasn't able to thank you earlier.
Thank you so much.
Let's meet after your win.
Either one of you must win.
- Me? The last man standing from P1?
- Right.
This makes no sense at all.
Head home first.
Right. I'll see you outside.
It was very sad.
When it's time for someone to leave,
all the times of joy and sorrow...
flash by in an instant.
After joining Bloody Game X,
it felt like a grand connection...
of all three seasons of Bloody Game.
The moments of Season One flashed by.
(Ji Min was a key player
in Bloody Game 1 5 years ago.)
The moments of Season Two
flashed by as well.
(She went across both sides
as a spy in Season 2.)
I can be a great liar.
I was a dealer in Season Three.
She's the lady of the house
in Bloody Game.
I was able to be with the ones...
I spent time with years ago.
- Pay me back! Thank you!
- I will.
It felt like I went back in time
to when I was that age.
I really had a great time.
As it was a team battle,
I was able to experience something I have
never experienced in the previous seasons.
There was a greater sense
of pleasure and joy.
There was also a great sense of rage.
I believe Bloody Game X...
will become the strongest memory
in my head.
Many people recognize me
because of Bloody Game.
I've met many of my supporters
through Bloody Game.
I think that was why I wanted
to show even more.
I believe I was able to go through
experiences and emotions...
that one might never experience in life.
I feel grateful for that...
and I won't be able to forget...
this season's Bloody Mansion.
- I'll see you outside.
- Great work.
Great work.
Gosh, I arrested the murderer yesterday
as the cop.
I'm actually taking her out now.
- Let's go.
- Right.
Great work.
- Great work.
- Right.
Things got intense toward the end.
I'm not the key figure.
Why do they all think that I am?
Right. That means YunB did well
to play the game.
Right.
Eight of you have survived
after all of the games.
Congratulations.
Tomorrow, the finalists of Bloody Game X
will be decided...
through the semi-finals.
"It's already the semi-finals?"
"Players will get eliminated
without mercy."
"I must stay on my toes from now on."
With my next plays,
I want to achieve a clean win...
which everyone will acknowledge.
I thought that I made it really far in.
When I first participated,
I said that I would be satisfied...
just to be able to reach the semi-finals.
After reaching the semi-finals,
I thought to myself,
"Will I be able to become to winner?"
No matter what game it is,
it'll be an individual battle.
It's a survival that's only meaningful
for the winner.
"I will go my way."
"No one should get in my way."
In Season Three,
I got eliminated
right before the semi-finals...
and I felt really disappointed.
My goal is obviously
to become the champion.
I must do my best.
I did feel nervous...
as I reached the semi-finals.
"I want to reach the finals."
I had this desire.
Whatever game is played,
I must do my best to stay focused
and to do well.
I must reach the finals
since I've made it this far.
Semi-finals?
With 7 players? No, with 8 players?
There are too many.
I must advance one more time...
to be able to say I have achieved my goal.
I don't think there's a chance for me
to get eliminated.
With the ones left,
I feel confident
to be able to beat every single one.
I will definitely make it to the finals.
I must...
become the champion.
I was known...
just as a calculator.
I was Ji Hoo-PT.
My heart that was empty...
has been filled
thanks to the love and sacrifice...
of the members of Team C and Team Rookie.
Just for the sake of giving joy...
to the ones who loved and trusted me,
I must...
become the champion.
Prepare for tomorrow's semi-finals.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)